I live off the boat, I don't want the boat
I'm a superhero, kid you like a zero
I play more roles than the narrow
I get pasta hip hop and watch it throw to the top
And like the real niggas lick the shot
My whole crew represents kids
And yo he did what he did
Even if he had the serve of day
I get sass to the edge and got a blest
And let him get the stress off his chest
I live off the boat, I don't want the boat
I'm saying I was up on these bricks is all about getting this
I was up on these bricks is all about getting this
what's happening everybody good morning
good afternoon good evening wherever you are wherever you're hanging out it is your am wake
up it it is uh what thursday the belief
Yeah. The 6th of July, I hope everybody had fantastic 4th of July and all that kind of
good stuff. Apologies for not getting a show out yesterday. I will get to that at some point
during the show, but first, since our guest is here, and what better way to kick off
after a day off than a nice mind-blowing conversation. Folks, the program, at least
the morning show for the first time, although we've had conversations on slow news day and the
free Assange Vigil series over the years. Fantastic to catch up, ladies and gentlemen.
John Kiriakou, CIA whistleblower, journalist, author, painter. I had, what, my lecturer,
motivational speaker? What all you got going on right now? John, I couldn't see you.
You know, a little bit here, a little bit there, and you can patch together a living.
Heck yeah. It is fantastic to see you. It's been a couple of years. I haven't had the
opportunity to catch up with you. It's a very crazy world that we're living in. It was weird
the last time we spoke since then. It's gotten significantly more absurd. Before we really get
into anything else, I would love to get your thoughts on this potential either, you know,
false flag or actual attack on the nuclear power station over in Russia, because they're,
I believe it's Ukraine, but they're basically, we've seen escalation towards a nuclear conflict
over the last 18 months really. And it's unsettling to say the least. And I would love to get your
thoughts on where we are right now, especially in light of Zelensky coming out, not only saying,
oh yeah, the CIA has been embedded here. We just try to keep them, you know, in the shadows,
but also all of the, I guess, nuclear escalation talk. Yeah, wow. There's so much to touch
on there, isn't there? I honestly think, and this may be a little upside down, but I honestly think
that the two sides, Russia and Ukraine, accusing each other of planning false flag operations
at the Zaporizhia power plant is what prevented an attack on the Zaporizhia power plant,
because they ratting each other out. I have no idea who might have been responsible for
even planning something like that, but the fact that they accused each other
made everybody focus on it. And then today, we saw a statement from the IAEA, the International
Atomic Energy Agency, which has inspectors on site. And they said that there are no
explosives at the plant. They're not sure how these accusations got started, but they said that
at least today, there's nothing to worry about. Although I got to say, I agree with you
that we're probably closer to some sort of nuclear situation, whether it's accidental or not,
than we have been in generations. And that's not good no matter how you look at it.
No, and there's, I mean, we've had 70 years of the ability to look at what happens when you
detonate a nuclear device. There's a little bit of argument in wiggle room as to how
fallout, how long the damage is, how wide of an area is affected. We've had tens of thousands
of nuclear devices set off in test form over the last 60, 70 years, which can't be great for
the planet. Can you imagine? Here we are all these years after the post-World War II testing
in the South Pacific. And we're just now offering money to the people who were affected and to
relocate their families because of nuclear contamination. We're talking about 70 years
after the end of the war. It's ridiculous. Yeah. And yet we're still marching on to
define new ways and I guess more creative ways to kill each other. So at least there's progress
on that front. Yeah. As the Ukraine situation becomes, I mean, visibly bad to even the casual
observer for NATO, for the Ukrainian regular army, they've been trying more and more Hollywood-esque
tactics in order to keep the Americans engaged or at least the average American observer engaged.
The whole thing with the Wagner-Merck pregosion. And then they did some sort of like MTV cribs thing
with his house the other day. Yeah. They're like, look, he's got this huge kitchen and look,
there's this tax of money and blood. Like, I don't understand the marketing behind what the
West is trying to do here in terms of either demonizing than briefly elevating, then going
back to sort of this odd demonizing of the Wagner group. Does this just kind of underscore
the outsized role that private military contractors play in modern combat? Where do you see that
particular war? I think so. I think that's exactly what it is. And it's funny too. The
only reason we're getting press coverage on it is because the Wagner group doesn't
belong to the United States. It's not run by Eric Prince, let's say. And so there's no real
desire or necessity in the American media to keep it secret. For example, we don't have any idea
what our own private armies or our own special forces for that matter are doing in places like
the Sahel or Somalia or Central Asia. We just don't know. It's not being reported.
But my God, the Wagner group does something and it's on every show.
And I think that to go to your point a moment ago about keeping Americans engaged on Ukraine,
I think that's the key because there's already been sort of crack in the foundation of the
Republican Party where they just don't want to keep writing these checks, these blank checks
to the Ukrainians. There was a report today that was published by NBC News saying that in April,
Richard Haas, who until last Friday was the president of the Council on Foreign Relations,
and two of his former deputies from the National Security Council who are now
fellows at the Council on Foreign Relations secretly met with the Russian foreign minister
at the United Nations in New York. This is something called Track 2 Diplomacy,
which means that it's unofficial diplomacy. It's diplomacy carried out by private citizens,
but in order to make it legal and constitutional it has to have the approval of the White House.
So we were told today by NBC News that Richard Haas and these two other men
met with Foreign Minister Sergei Lavrov in April to lay the groundwork for what would
eventually become peace talks between the Russians and the Ukrainians,
which really means between the Russians and the Americans.
Nobody ran screaming from the room reportedly, so that's supposed to be a positive. We don't
know if anything was agreed upon. We don't know if there have been subsequent meetings,
but at the very least they've made this plan or they've established this channel to get together
so when the political situation necessitates actual diplomacy, there's a mechanism by which
we can do that. It's a good thing. Yeah, and I mean having Ukrainian peace brokered by the
Council on Foreign Relations is pretty par for the course, but there's...
Can I comment on that? May I interrupt you for one minute? Certainly.
Certainly. You know, this is like the greatest fear of the United States,
and that is that the Chinese are going to become involved somehow. Just in the last six months,
we saw the Chinese broker piece between Iran and Saudi Arabia, between Saudi Arabia and Syria,
between Saudi Arabia and Yemen. We want to keep the Chinese out of the Ukraine conflict
at all costs, and we're pretending that the Russians are not friendly with the Chinese.
The truth of the matter is the Chinese don't have a dog in this fight, and the Chinese spend their
money on economic development rather than on weapons. And so the Chinese actually would be
honest brokers in this thing, but a consequence of that is that it pushes us out of the equation.
We like to pretend that we're neutral. We like to pretend that the world sees us as being neutral.
We're not neutral, and Chinese involvement would prove that we're not neutral, and we can't afford
to that happen. Well, no, and there's, especially to that point, when you've got those Republicans
standing up in Congress, as you mentioned, saying, I don't want to write another blank
check to Ukraine, it's because most of them want to write that blank check to Taiwan.
Most of them would rather be involved in a direct conflict with China,
rather than get bogged down in Eastern Europe for the next 10 years.
Oh, I'll tell you what, during the 2016 election, I remember sitting with a family friend who was
in her 80s.
And, you know, all she does is sit and watch TV all day long.
And we were talking about the election, and she said, oh, I'm not voting for Biden.
Was it 2016?
No, I'm sorry, 2020.
I'm not voting for Biden.
And I said, why not?
And she said, well, Biden's with China.
And I said, what do you mean by that?
He's with China.
And she just kind of looked at me like she wasn't even sure what she meant.
And I said, you watch way too much Fox News.
Way too much.
Not wanting to bomb China does not mean you're with China.
Now with that said, I actually fear the Biden foreign policy on China because I think it's
just as provocative as the Trump foreign policy was toward China.
I'm worried about these confrontations in the South China Sea, in the Straits of Taiwan.
I'm worried about sending F-35s to Taiwan and guided missile systems and things like
that.
You know, if anything, we should be at the negotiating table with the Chinese, not poking
the hornet's nest.
And that's really what we've been doing.
It seems like the neocon death cult that took root 40 some years ago has become this
sort of self-perpetuating machine where everybody gets promoted from inside the house, where falling
up is the standard for success, where previous failures just mean that you're going to fit
in perfectly when the scheme shifts for a different region in a geopolitical conflict.
And go ahead, dude, just yesterday, Elliot Abrams.
I was going to bring that up.
Elliot Abrams was named to the Presidential Advisory Board on public diplomacy.
This is a guy who was Ronald Reagan's Assistant Secretary of State for Latin America who was
in up to his neck with Iran-Contra and ended up pleading guilty to two counts of obstruction
of justice over the Iran-Contra scandal.
He was pardoned by George H.W. Bush.
Then he went to work for George W. Bush and helped to perpetuate the lie that Saddam Hussein
had weapons of mass destruction.
And then during the Trump administration, he was the special envoy for Iran and then
for Venezuela that withdrew us from the JCPOA and then tried to install this pretender
to the throne Juan Guaido in the presidency of Venezuela.
And now he's working for the Biden administration on public policy advocacy.
This is just a euphemism for propaganda.
And it goes to show you that there is no difference between the neoliberal foreign policy and
the neo-conservative foreign policy.
It's exactly the same and the players are interchangeable.
And it really is the meme where you've got the jet flying by dropping bombs and
then you've got the jet flying by dropping bombs with a rainbow flag and a Black Lives Matter sticker
or whatever.
That's the foreign policy.
We have to stay in Afghanistan, John, because the women need to drive and vote.
That's why we're doing it for women's rights.
We've been in Somalia, South Sudan, and all of these countries in central and western
Africa for the last 15 years because freedom, I don't know.
And then Wagner Group pops up all over the place in those regions so you get little snippets
of reporting based on what Wagner Group's doing.
But they don't ever say why a Russian private military contracting firm is in those regions
because then they'd have to be like, well, turns out that the State Department's funding
this terror group, the CIA's funding that terror group, and those groups are fighting
this group.
Sometimes they fight each other.
So we've just got to make sure that all of the weapons go in and they can sort
it out.
And that's what's happening in places like Libya and Afghanistan.
In Libya, the CIA supports one faction and the State Department supports another faction,
and they actually fight each other, which is just nuts.
It's insane.
In Afghanistan, when I was on the Senate Foreign Relations Committee staff, we had
a group of Afghan women, intellectuals, come to talk to us.
And one woman said something that has stuck in my mind for the last, what, 12 years.
She said, look, if you haven't been able to secure the country after 10 years of nation
building, it's because we don't want you.
She said something that was even more important.
She said, the Taliban did not come down from outer space and just land in Afghanistan.
We are our sons and our brothers and our husbands.
If the Taliban is ascended, it's because we want the Taliban.
And she was exactly right.
We can't understand how we lost Afghanistan.
We lost Afghanistan because they never wanted us there in the first place.
And that should be a lesson learned in foreign policy that we just have chosen to ignore.
Well, instead, it seems like what we do is pick a particular region based on what's under
the ground or where they're located strategically.
Oh, there we are.
Hit them with the prospect of an IMF loan, bury them in debt and then, you know, tell
them, well, we can collect one way or another.
But your neighbors have some resources that we would like to seem to have lost
your sound there for a second.
Oh, yeah, go into your settings on the stream yard there.
It's the little sprocket cog thingy.
Maybe there's something in there.
OK, sounds good.
That was fun.
Usually the tech gremlins are on my side.
Let's go ahead and pop and check in with you guys here for a moment to see what we got going
on.
Wow, my machine's running a little slow.
And there we go.
Oh, right.
Fantastic.
Glad I got sort of, I was just saying, usually the tech gremlins are on my side.
Well, you know what, your video went out just for a second.
Mine was OK.
And then I just lost your sound.
Weird.
Yeah, OK, so then they probably are.
I don't know.
I'm kind of in the sticks here, too.
I don't know if you can, but it looks, it looks very pretty.
Oh, it's beautiful.
I'm in Sonoma County, big trees.
I'm about 15 minutes from the coast.
Fantastic.
I didn't realize you were in Sonoma.
It's awesome there.
I love it.
I could live there.
Yeah, I'm planning on it.
Rest of my days.
I dig it.
I'm I'm all for it.
We were, yeah, is Creek Beach.
Like, yeah, fantastic.
Good times.
Went and saw a rodeo last week.
I don't know, the fun stuff.
Sweet.
Anyway, yeah, no, just like actual super dorky Americana
kitch, freaking the Norman Rockwell make you puke wholesomeness.
It was it was awesome.
It was good times.
I we have seen John and I don't want to jump around too much.
And I would kind of like to just hang out in geopolitics for a moment.
But but we've seen a a flurry of whistleblowers over the last couple of years
come forward with information that just seem to reinforce a
a ongoing state narrative that we've got to do more censorship.
And we've got to clamp down on people more.
There is the Facebook, not a whistleblower whistleblower Francis Hagen.
Hagen, there was some white hacker that used to work at Twitter,
whose solution was more censorship.
We've had people come out talking about aliens lately.
Is there in your opinion, is there an effort to kind of
smudge the definition of of what a whistleblower is in the same way that the
Twitter files were just screenshots.
And that's what journalism is now.
You don't get primary source, anything anymore.
Is there an attempt to kind of shift the perspective of what blowing
the whistle on something actually means and what does that do in terms
of getting legitimate information out into the public?
Oh, yeah, that's a that's a very important question, actually.
There's actually a legal definition of whistleblowing.
Many people don't know this.
It's bringing to light any evidence of waste, fraud, abuse,
illegality or threats to the public health or public safety.
So Francis Francis Hagen, in my view, is not only not a whistleblower,
she's just a corporate spokesperson.
What was her her motivation for coming forward?
Her motivation was to make Facebook a stronger company.
Her motivation was to was to improve Facebook's bottom line.
It wasn't to expose wrongdoing.
The half.
hacker you mentioned from Twitter, same thing. That hacker was working with officers of the
CIA and the FBI and the NSA to squelch free speech on Twitter. And you're absolutely right
when you say that we generally don't get primary source documentation. We hear so
often and I say this like a mantra. We hear so often about wrongdoing or allegations of
wrongdoing. And then we're not given access to the evidence, to the actual primary source
documents. Well, if you're going to throw a grenade into the middle of the room, don't
expect people just to nod their heads and thank you for it. I want to see what the
evidence is. I'm a smart enough guy. You're a smart enough guy. We can figure out
the truth, but you have to lay out the evidence. If you're going to make an accusation and
call yourself a whistleblower, let me decide that. Let me judge you. And that's just not
what we're seeing. You know, it's not even that or I shouldn't say it even. I should
say it's not. I'm not also that this has gotten too terribly much better with with
Elon Musk at Twitter, although I'm far closer to Musk than to anybody else like
Zuckerberg on issues of free speech. But Twitter, just like Facebook and Instagram
and LinkedIn and everywhere else is is replete with former CIA officers who took
the pension and then cashed in to make the big bucks with these tech firms. And
so many of them, when they leave the CIA, don't really leave the CIA. You maintain
those relationships. You talk to people there. They can email you and say, Hey,
there's this account that's given us some trouble. You mind banning them or
blocking them or whatever. That happens all the time. And no corporation, no
social media outlet has come up with with a way to ensure people's
constitutionally protected rights of free speech by keeping the likes of the CIA
and the FBI and NSA and Homeland Security at bay. We're just not there yet.
Well, and it doesn't seem like it doesn't seem like the companies
themselves get much of an opportunity even from their inception to push back on
it, given that so many of them are either bought out initially by or are
funded with seed money from like Incutel or some sort of, you know,
intelligence attached incubator. Yeah, that's an important point. Most
Americans have never heard of Incutel. They don't know what Incutel
is. In fact, Incutel is the CIA's venture capital arm. It's a quasi
governmental, well, I'm going to call it a FinTech bank, for lack of a better
term, where the CIA invests millions and millions of dollars in young tech
firms, knowing that the CIA can later use the technology that they're
developing. Well, some of those tech firms turn into major multi billion
dollar concerns, and the CIA's got tentacles in them that go all the way
to the CEO's office. Yeah, I mean, look at Mark Zuckerberg. The Facebook
launched the day LifeLog was shut down. It was incubated with the help of
Incutel money. That's right. And now, I mean, arguably, one of the, if not the
largest, you know, social media platform on the planet, the meta or whatever
that's evolving into may not be doing great. They just, although they did
just launch their Twitter alternative, they got 12 million or so people
signing up on the first day. They're gonna fight. Who do you got in the
Musk Zuckerberg fight, John Kiriakou? You know, I'm actually a cheap SOB. And I
generally, not generally, I've never in my life paid for a pay per view. I
would pay for that pay per view. Musk and Zuckerberg in a cage match. I'm
going with Musk. Okay, okay. I did. You know what? I tend to believe you.
There's there's a couple of different ways to look at him. He is a
bigger fella. Mark Zuckerberg definitely more wiry, more jiu-jitsu
training, a little bit, you know, probably a little bit more confident. But I
think that if you punched Elon Musk, he would, he would like red out, you know,
the mist would come down and then like, you'd have to have four guys
pulling him off and then he'd be, you'd have to like whisper like
cerulean blue or something to bring him out of it. And it would just be
chaos. I'll tell you what, though, I usually have an in on the the pirate
stream for that, the bootleg stream for all the UFC fights and stuff. I'll
hook you up. I will. Hey, thank you. Thank you. Thank you. I'll take it. This
is ridiculous. I mean, this is this is parody movie cartoon level two
billionaires fighting in the Coliseum for no reason whatsoever. This is
what we've come to as a country, great country we have here. I don't understand
this at all. Look, if there was, you know, if inflation was lower, if there
was, you know, more people, less homeless, more people, where we had
cleaner, cleaner water and a couple of billionaires wanted to fight, that'd
be great. That'd be great. But it was just a couple of years ago that
Elon Musk said that he was going to end global hunger. Remember that? I
do. Whatever happened to that? Right after that, those Taiwanese kids got
trapped right in the cave or something like that. And Elon Musk stopped
talking about world hunger all together. He had to make some sub or
something like that to go find him. And it took the heat entirely off of
the I'm gonna end world hunger thing. Yeah. And then I think six
months later, they locked down the planet. And people just sort of
forgot about that's right. That's right. And I'm still waiting for the
hyperloop from LA to San Francisco that he was supposed to pay
for.
Well, I think he switched from that from now it's LA to Vegas is
what he's working on, which is the dumbest thing on the face of
the earth anyway, because then you're just going to be stuck in
traffic for seven hours one way underground.
That's right. And I mean, I don't like being underground in very
much in particular anyway, you know, it just it's not not a
comfortable space for me. I can't imagine being in a traffic jam in
an underground tunnel for like hours, no way.
No, crazy.
She has
And then the there was a it did not having anything to do with Elon
Musk or hyperloop, but at least California politics. There was
the proposed high speed rail that just got completely scrapped and
abandoned. That's right. That it's I mean, that's approaching
Alaska Bridge to nowhere levels of non completion useless
project. I and it could be a beneficial thing for the state. It
could, in fact, employ tens of thousands of people annually if
not, you know, if not a little more, it could provide mass rapid
transportation between places that are generally, you know, very
inconvenient to get to from me to get to the San Francisco
airport, even though it's technically only like 70
miles, it takes three and a half hours. Oh my God, you know, we
have the same situation here on the East Coast. I'm in
Washington, of course, and we've got Amtrak, you can go to to
New York and Boston, but it's it's slow slow slow. And the
reason it's slow is is crazy, because there's a tunnel just
north of Baltimore that was built in 1850. And if we
went to high speed rail, the tunnels too narrow to accommodate
a high speed rail train. And so the trains have to fit through
that tunnel. It's it's the craziest thing. You know, like
why why don't we have high speed rail between, let's say,
Boston and New York and Washington, or New York and
Chicago, or New York and Atlanta or Miami or whatever, we
should have one, the Chinese get all this high speed train.
Why don't we have any of it? And why does it cost me $300 to take
the train to New York and back and $200 to fly to New York and
back? That doesn't make any sense.
No, no, it doesn't. It really doesn't. Although I guess you
could argue that less people are riding the train than they
are flying. But I don't you know, I mean, what it
basically amounts to is there's a public private
partnership between most of these major corporations and the
government. And they're allowed to gouge based on because we can
yeah, because you're you're still gonna pay, you still have
to get to work. You know, we did a there was a story a few
months ago about a guy who
Chinese man who had ran afoul of their social credit, and so they took away his bus pass or his train pass and so his
two-hour commute to work became a 14-hour one on buses and until he, you know,
had shown him sequence or whatever effectively that was his life. Well, this
happens in the U.S. all the time, but in different ways. You get a little bit behind on a payment. Next thing,
you know, you're in a debt spiral that results in you,
you know, the not being able to afford to pay the registration on your vehicle or something like that.
You can't do this. Then that stacks up and all of a sudden your
25-minute ride to work has turned into a four-hour bus ride or a nine-hour, you know, pedal or whatever it is.
Yeah, that's absolutely true.
Absolutely true. We think that
that we don't face the same challenges that so many other people in the world do and and we do.
It doesn't matter how wealthy of a country we are. Oftentimes, the deck is still stacked.
Well, and there's, I mean, it's such a clear cut
tiered system in terms of predetermined winners and losers, not just economically, but via whatever passes for a justice system.
The most obvious example recently is Hunter Biden.
What's even more fascinating to me, not that the president has a crack head son,
or that he's going out of his way to obstruct an investigation into or anything like that.
The marketing behind Joe Biden,
regardless of how much irony and is involved in these statements, is that he's, you know, a family man
and that cares about the people and he's a man of the people.
And then you find out that, like, his half illegitimate grandkid isn't allowed to be mentioned in the White House
and all that stuff. They're finally asking questions about it.
They, this is the most obvious setup I've ever seen in my life.
John, why did we hear that they found cocaine in the West Wing?
Why is that even a story?
Yeah, it shouldn't be a story.
And, you know what, it's it's being prolonged artificially, too.
So what happened was when you go into the White House, especially when you go into a secure area,
you can't take a cell phone in there, right?
It's it's a security violation.
So you have to leave your cell phone in a little cubby.
They have these cubbies attached to the wall with slats in them
outside of every what's called a vaulted area,
an area where classified conversations may take place.
So somebody pulled this phone out.
There was a little packet of coke apparently stuck to the phone somehow.
Put it in the cubby, got his phone later.
The coke became detached in the little baggy state in the in the slat.
Well, it's not like you can just walk in off the street
and go into the West Wing of the Oval Office.
They know exactly who's in there.
And you if you're going in, you know, there's a clearance process.
Even if you don't have a security clearance, you have to provide a social security number.
They do a background check on you.
Law enforcement check to see if, you know, you've got any any legal issues in your background.
So they know exactly who has been in the White House.
They know exactly who has been in those meetings.
Now, whether it's an outsider or a member of the White House staff,
what they also have is your fingerprints, right?
Because to get a job that requires a clearance requires fingerprints.
And there's no possible way anybody can tell me that there aren't fingerprints on that baggy.
Of course, there are fingerprints on the baggy.
So run the fingerprints, which takes, you know, a couple of hours.
Identify the person and then do what you're going to do.
But this is blown up into this major issue.
Donald Trump is is saying on social, what's it called, Truth Social,
that it was Hunter Biden's Coke and the Special Counsel's Coke and Joe Biden's Coke.
And that they were all doing the Coke together.
The Secret Service said today that they're investigating.
They're on the case.
Well, my God, investigating means just run the fingerprint and then cross match it
with everybody who was on the schedule that day.
It takes a minute.
My guess is we're never going to know or we'll never know
who belongs to that Coke, and it's just going to go away.
But why is this a story anyway?
Take the Coke, destroy it, and let's move on to more important issues.
Right. Right.
And so this is there.
There's a couple of things that that are kind of the, I don't know,
raise a forest of red flags for me.
And it makes me wonder, like, what what the actual story of the day was
because cocaine in Washington, D.C. Oh, no, color me surprised.
You know, like, yeah, I'll tell you, I'll tell you a funny story.
When I was when I was 18 years old, I worked as a paid intern for my congressman
and I was in the district office in Beaver Falls, Pennsylvania.
And my dad called me one day at the office and he said,
are you in some kind of trouble?
And I said, no, why?
And he said, because an FBI agent was here and he wanted to talk to you.
And I freaked out. I was a kid. I was 18.
This FBI agent left a card with a number.
Please call me.
So I called the guy and I said, my dad told me that you wanted to talk to me.
He came to our house and and he said,
have you ever seen the congressman snort cocaine?
And I was like, what? No.
Have you ever seen anybody in the office snort cocaine?
I said, no.
Have you ever seen the congressman trade stamps for cocaine?
And I was like, no.
And I was so freaked out.
I blurted out, they all smoke pot on Friday afternoons.
Well, it turned out that the congressman was trading stamps for cocaine
and ended up going to prison for seven and a half years.
But scared the crap out of me.
And he wasn't the only one.
It was like four or five congressmen ended up either losing their primaries
or being prosecuted and going to prison because there was this
coke ring on Capitol Hill that was in 1983.
And I came to learn after, you know, 41 years here,
that's just how Washington runs.
It's just a fact of life.
Yeah, I mean, I look, I never worked inside the district itself.
I had a friend who was the lead bartender
at McCormick and Schmicks for a very long time.
Directly across the street from me, I can see it from here.
Yeah.
And so we would go in and get like the Rockstar treatment.
And as long as we kept paying for oysters, you know, Greg would keep
throwing the booze at us.
And I can't tell you how many, you know, Senate and congressional
aides and lobbyists or whatever, we saw get up in pairs or threes
and go to the bathroom and then come back.
I mean, the entire time we were hanging out there and I mean, look,
it it doesn't take a brain surgeon or a habitual addict to realize
what's going on when something like that happens, that routine.
And I mean, it's just it's a you're right.
It's how the city runs.
I there's it's only to distract from something else that is making this
going, you know, making this a thing and stay in the news.
And I don't know if it's to cover for the fact that every time they
let Joe Biden out in public and on camera, he proves to the world
that he's in severe cognitive decline.
You know, it it's bad.
Did you see any of the Fourth of July stuff?
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
The worry is like, I just want to say hi.
Yeah, I want me to sing.
And it's like, buddy.
Yeah.
There was a poll that came out today saying that 30 percent of registered
Democrats don't want him to run for president.
And he's actually losing to Trump in every swing state.
I mean, that's that's got to be a crystal clear message
to the Democratic establishment.
And it's not.
So there's been a fair amount of speculation, not unwarranted,
I don't think about the the the road to getting Gavin Newsom
into that candidate seat in 2024.
And as detrimental to the country as Gavin Newsom
as president would be, if you guys can get him out of California,
we sure would appreciate it. We would.
You know, he went to I know a couple of days ago
as a Biden surrogate, Biden's only going to get 24, 25 percent in Idaho.
So why he would go to Idaho is a mystery.
But the fact that he went to Idaho is what's newsworthy.
He went because he was asked to.
He is doing everything that the Biden people want him to do.
And I think that he's doing it for the reason that you cite.
I think that he thinks that there's a chance
that Joe Biden simply is not going to be the nominee
because he's not going to make it all the way to the nominating convention.
There's going to.
a hole. Everybody hates Kamala Harris. She's the most unpopular vice president since Spiro Agnew
and there's going to be this opening for Gavin Newsom to be coordinated next August or September.
Yeah. Yeah. And let's also remember that Dick Cheney was a vice president between Agnew and
Harris and he shot a guy in the face after being openly evil for six years out loud at that point.
I mean, there was a cartoon on Cartoon Network where they didn't even draw his face. It was just
a Darth Vader helmet. Kamala Harris, more unlikable than that guy. That's bad. It's bad.
And so with Bobby Kennedy Jr. throwing his hat in the ring and him actually starting to pull well
now, the Democrats have to do something. Gavin Newsom, arguably as handsome, full head of dark hair,
not gray hair, and he can wear a pullover and talk in a soft reassuring voice. And I think
that that's good enough for the Democratic Party because he's a team player. He's a Pelosi relative.
He married into Jerry Brown's family with his first marriage. Oh, yeah.
The, you know, I mean, he has been a, you know, he was basically lab grown for Governor of
California. Yeah. And he's a, he's the consummate insider. You know, he may come
across to those of us not in California as this kind of slightly rogue left of center liberal savior.
He's very much a DNC insider, but he looks like he's a young wave maker from the outside. He's,
he's not, and, and politically he's playing this very well. He's waiting his turn and hoping
that things turn out for him sooner rather than later. Surviving the recall election.
Yeah. And, and by basically saying absolutely nothing. And then when asked questions,
blatantly lying to the camera and then doing the exact opposite. Once he got back into that,
see, I mean, that's, you know, that's, that's, that's mayor of Chicago style.
Yeah. I'm gonna wait out this door. Benjamin Netanyahu did almost the exact same thing.
Yeah. But you know, where he sat up, they had that, that rotating door, revolving door of
prime ministers there for a moment. Now he's back in the driver's seat, whether the
ethics investigation stuff sat out COVID. And then came back in talking about, oh, yeah,
we've got a genetic and biological database for everybody who lives here. Thanks to this
pandemic. Now we're going to roll forward with marketing that we've got some friends from
Union 8200 that have new software company that just popped up. Boy, you're going to want to listen
to their pitch. And I mean, they're just rolling with it. It's wild to watch. Janine,
and I wanted to talk to you about this. When Netanyahu came back in, even after
Naftali Bennett left, and Naftali Bennett openly, I think more to the right than
Bibi, at least on paper. Netanyahu came in with a literal vengeance. And we have seen,
most recently, just the most blatant brazen war crimes that were committed in Palestine.
Last year, when they were doing this, there was a little bit of a collapse of the narrative
that Israel is only doing these things for good. One, I guess, like, what's your overall view of
how Israel's moving forward with this completely murderous government? And then is there a
sell-by date on that for American support? That answer is an easy no. No. We'll support Israel
no matter how murderous and how right-wing extremists it becomes. This is already the most
right-wing extremist government in the history of Israel. When you've got the likes of
Itamar Ben Gavir, for example, as the Minister of National Security, and Smotrich, what's his
first name, as Minister of Finance, but with military authority over the West Bank,
willing to commit war crimes, and these are guys who have been convicted of felony hate
crimes against Palestinians. These are guys who have celebrated people who have committed
crimes against humanity against Palestinians. There's no hope for peace. This incursion that
we saw in Tingenin a couple of days ago that resulted, now they're telling us nine Palestinians
dead, about a hundred wounded, and then they apparently pulled out. This is just the very
beginning. Now to me, the only real threat to Netanyahu has nothing to do with the Palestinians.
The threat is this takeover of the court system. Yesterday, Netanyahu fired the chief of police
of Tel Aviv. This guy is wildly popular and is seen as a moderate. And the reason why he was
fired is he does not support Likud's takeover of the courts. And Netanyahu is a great politician.
He can really read a crowd. And he delayed this takeover last April, thinking that it would blow
over the national strikes that we were seeing that included policemen and members of the
military would subside, and they haven't subsided. They've come roaring back. We saw a massive
demonstration in Tel Aviv just a couple of days ago, a demonstration that was so big it actually
shut down Ben Gurion Airport, the international airport. So I think that on this issue of what
he's calling judicial reform, Netanyahu may have overstepped. If there's anything that maybe
possibly might could take down the government, it would be that. With that said, the Israeli
electorate, because of the influx of so many Russian and Ukrainian Jews over the last 10
or 15 years, has moved so far to the right that I don't think we'll ever see a viable
socialist movement again. I don't think we'll ever see a viable labor party again.
It's just the question is going to be, are you going to vote for a right-wing government,
a far right-wing government, or an extreme right-wing government? Those are their choices.
Well, and it seems like that's what Europe is going to get handed over the next several years
too. The not just France, but Germany, Italy, a number of NATO. Hungary, Poland.
Yeah. And as I guess 50, 60 years of neoliberal experimentation comes to its natural conclusion,
because of the marketing, because of propaganda efforts, because of just, I guess, complete corporate
capture, most of Western Europe is now in a very similar situation where it's a right-wing,
a far right-wing, or an extremist right-wing government that are your choices, or you have a
completely corporate captured and insane entity like the German Green Party as an alternative.
Yeah. I think you're exactly right. So much has been made in the press just over the past
week about the ascendance of the far right in France and in Italy. Italy has a fascist
prime minister right now. And the most popular party, at least if public opinion polls are to be
believed, is the extreme right party in France. But Greece had its elections two weeks ago,
and eight parties won seats in parliament. Six of them are right-wing parties,
and four of them are right-wing extremist parties. There are two neo-Nazi parties that
won a total of 13 seats in the Greek parliament. This is a very disturbing trend that we're seeing
all over Western Europe. And we already are seeing entrenched right-wing parties in Poland,
in Hungary, in the UK, let's be honest. When they're scooping up refugees off the streets
and then putting them on planes and sending them to Rwanda for resettlement, I mean that's a right-wing
extremist policy and it's probably illegal. Probably is.
So I guess historically we would be trading one corporate captured entity for another
corporate captured entity with better fancier uniforms or like jaunty or hats or something
like that. And I've always been of the mindset that...
I'm going to stand in opposition to the authoritarian regardless of what color uniform they're wearing
or the shape of the hat. I don't care. It's the the ideology behind it that I'm opposed to.
It is fascinating to me how it with such a blatant display of why
top-down corporate ran politics is a failure when done by what's perceived as the left how easily
and arguably more corporate ran more fascistic or more authoritarian entity on the right can just
I mean be like look no those those guys are terrible because of their stupid social stuff
but we're gonna do all the same thing economically only worse just sign up for it and we won't let
your kids look at drag queens or something like that and that's good enough yeah you're exactly
right it's a mystery to me how it is that Americans don't understand that their choices
are a right of center party and a further right of center party and that's it that's it listen
there's nothing progressive about the democratic party nothing at all if the democrats and the
republicans are simply two capitalist parties two sides of the same coin we don't have
sorry but until corner west join the green party their frontrunner or their presumptive
nominee would all pro-ukrainian war too oh yeah sure sure that's absolutely true
yeah and and if you're opposed to the war in your crane in Ukraine you're a russian propagandist
yeah that's what they're that's what they're calling Bob Kennedy in today's New York Times
that he's a conspiracy theorist and a russian propagandist well so they have to regardless
of what rfk jr has has you know said himself about his positions on you know vaccines he's
always going to be an anti-vaxxer regardless of the fact that his son went through Ukraine
fought came back had his personal story that he told his father which apparently changed his
position on Ukraine that still makes him a russian agent right it's the the the fantasy
it is so much more easy for people to believe than what is the nuanced reality and it's be
we've just been so dumbed down john we've been so conditioned to hyper react to even half of a
headline and not process any of this information we've outsourced all of our critical thinking and
it's left a populace that it is so easily driven and easily manipulated that you can sell them
someone like Gavin Newsom or Joe Biden as a president and and peter hotez is the picture of health
yeah and robert f kennedy jr as you know a tin foil hat wearing crackpot who is out there eating
nuts and berries to cure cancer or something and like and people go yeah that makes sense
right right and you know americans have no mind for history either um
bill clinton when he was president promised boris yeltsin that the united states would not
permit ukraine to join nato barack obama when he was president promised vladimir putin that the
united states would not permit ukraine to join nato we've known for a generation that this has been
a russian red line they don't care if the ukrainians join the european union they don't care
but they were adamant that ukraine not joined nato and then we overthrew the ukrainian
government in 2014 that was opposed to joining nato and installed a government that wanted to
join nato and then we announced you know what we would love to have the ukrainians in nato
well what did we think was going to happen did we think that the russians which have a
an enormous border with ukraine that has ethnic russians living in major enclaves
on the ukraine side of the border would not intervene can you imagine if this were happening
in canada or in mexico we we would have gone nuclear by now and most americans just don't
understand that they they have this romantic view of you know the ukrainians standing alone
against the russian bear and then the americans running to their side to preserve freedom and
democracy you remember what people used to say uh after 9 11 they attacked us because they hate
our freedom well it's the same kind of silly nonsensical propaganda in this uh in this ukraine
conflict people just don't understand what the history of the thing is well a history is something
that people are in the minds that are at least with pundits and then it becomes the kind of
an infection takes root in the mind of the the citizenry but history begins whenever it's
politically convenient there's never any acknowledgement of anything that may have led
up to that because time hadn't started yet and then everything that happens forward is a direct
result of whatever we said our imaginary bad guy did that started history and people are just
very orwellian in the way that it it plays out so true so true and it's going to come back and
bite us i think it i mean in many many ways it is and you see this with real-time narrative
collapse throughout this ukraine conflict every time that there's been a major incident
Nord Stream the Crimean bridge there was the rocket attack that landed in Poland that you know
i mean people in the west were screaming for russian blood over it for about 10 minutes and
then the independent media all over the place was like no no no no no no we we actually have
the the stats for this no this is how this happened so there's been um and i did garland
nixon and i talk about this all the time um there's the establishment media now has to
incorporate what we do in the independent media as part of their breaking news it used to be we
never existed then we only existed as crazy people in our mother's basements and then
we only existed in the nether regions of youtube now it's okay breaking you know this outlet out of
nowhere's vill is reporting that this thing you know and so they've got to spin around it react to
it but we are because and this is why they're cracking down on the internet so far because of
social media because of the internet we are finally in a place where we are competing with
the people that that make us react to the i guess manufacturing of reality in real time
but but we're on the ground watching in so many different places that they've got a
they've got to change their approach to propaganda because of the effectiveness of the medium
that's right and that's why we need independent media more now than we ever have before
yeah yeah that's fair and it's i mean in light of things like the restrict act in light of all
of the things like these hate speech laws that are coming out of western europe where hate speech
just means if you contradict the narrative you're you're wrong and we're coming after you yes um
there's got to be some sort of i don't know that
what would your i mean do you he did counterterrorism you know how to look at the long picture you
don't look at the big picture you understand how a lot of moving parts work it where do you see
the future of legitimate independent media and journalism going in light of all of these
legislative and non-legislative measures to stifle it to filter it to siphon all that that
it's going to be a difficult slog for a couple of reasons first of all you have the institutional
corporate outlets that that do everything they can to squelch independent voices
secondly there is little to no budget anywhere for investigative journalism real
investigative journalism with a handful of exceptions pro-publica is fantastic and
quasi think tanks like the brennan center fantastic our friends at the gray zone amazing
work for almost no money and and third is is the quickness with which people will accuse you of
being uh under the control or in the pay of the enemy you know again if if you don't
if you don't toe the line on something like ukraine you're a russian propagandist if you
don't toe the line on taiwan you're a chinese propagandist if you don't toe the line on
venezuela you're a communist
propagandist and you're not you're just looking for the actual truth on the
ground that's not filtered through some multi-billion dollar conglomerate
somewhere or through the White House the State Department or the CIA and it's
hard to find. I do think though that they're because that's so
saturated with noise that when you do get a hold of people who do legitimate
work they sort of you know sort of rise to the top rather quickly. The Grey Zone
certainly Vanessa Beley has always done tremendous work covering Syria and that
conflict of Bartlett goes everywhere that she wants to write about and that's
fantastic. Whitney Webb at Unlimited Hangout has done some incredible
investigative work over the last several years getting ready to add a volume to the
two-part book on the Epstein series now. So I mean the the opportunity for it's
there what what I see is a tendency to hypersensationalize on a couple of
major ideological or political points rather than sort of dissecting the
substance of the issue. However I'll still take that over blatant propaganda and
I'll still take that or you know it's not like you shouldn't have an opinion about
it. Did you see Max Blumenthal deliver his statements in front of the UN
Security Council the other day? I sure did. I sure did. That it it's a shame
that it fell on so many deaf ears because I really do feel like that is the
sort of statement you those are the statements that more and more American
journalists need to be making not John just if they get invited to a room like
that but in general in all of their reporting because this is very very
serious shit and people are treating it like it's a freaking video game. Yeah
absolutely true couldn't agree more. I know how much time you had John if you
had an hour please you know let people know where they can how they can keep up
with what you have. Oh thank you I appreciate it I'm on Twitter at John
Kiriakou I'm on Facebook I do a daily show that's carried on rumble called
political misfits and in the next few weeks I'm gonna start a podcast I'm
gonna try my hand there I'm also more importantly on sub-stack and I say
more importantly because that's where I put everything I do sub-stack I'm at John
Kiriakou. Oh and before you get out of here there is a game that we always play
with with new guests on the show and even though we've spoke before us first
time on the morning show there's a studies of confirmed that music will
help with patients who are experiencing cognitive decline tap into parts of
their lives and access full memories. Let's say God forbid you John Kiriakou are
in the old whistleblowers home you got a case of the Joe Bidens all right. Can
you think of a piece or two or whatever music that would bring you back give
you some memory recall? Oh yeah I'll have to think too hard about it. I don't have to think at
all about it. I listen to two kinds of music I listen to classic rock and I
listen to Greek folk music that my parents and grandparents used to play
when I was growing up so every morning as soon as I roll over in bed I put on
70s on 7 or a classic vinyl on Sirius XM and if I'm feeling particularly down I
go to something called rebetiko music which is music that came out of the
the opium dens of Constantinople in the 1920s and 1930s. Wild all right
excellent thank you very much yeah yeah this is a fun game John Kiriakou thank you
so much for for being generous with your time being on the show thank you good
to see you good to see you too we will we'll do this more than every couple of
years though fantastic all right take care my friend thank you bye bye John
Kiriakou ladies and gentlemen always a pleasure talk to that fella
yeah Thursday so you guys I'm I'm really sorry that I did not get a show in I spent
my fourth of July in the most retarded fashion we we did the show and then
got gear situated thrown in the car went in to uh
to Ashley's dad's house picked up his truck trailer and then drove to Sacramento
it was about three hours away got there around two o'clock nice the hottest part of the day
was balmy 100 or so degrees and then started tearing apart a shed but we couldn't tear it apart
we had to painstakingly pull it apart because it's supposed to come back here and then get rebuilt
that was like an eight hour mission and it sucked a lot uh I got
it got more sawdust in me via my eyeballs and nostrils then most people get by eating
subway all year uh which resolved so she wound up driving back with the shed in the back of the
trailer decided to get Burger King at midnight so why not got the trailer stuck so I had to back it out
with like 80% of my vision back it out of a drive through I don't know how many of you have ever
read the opportunity of reversing uh a the trailer before but it's you know it it's it it takes some
skill it does it's not not you can't just hop in uh fun times fun times got back around um
uh two or three in the morning but all said and done and slept through all of my alarms
but it just did it didn't didn't happen um but also like
just sort of shit uh but uh you know eventually it'll turn into something good um
wow I yeah it was all it was a long day well for basically 22 hours straight of just work and drive
and work and drive yeah yeah and so I apologize for not getting the show out yesterday uh
it it sucked on every level um oh let me go over here I have our Twitter DM screwed up for everybody
else too or am I just lucky I have not been able to send a freaking DM for several hours
okay well no it looks like the okay it looks like the uh promo tweets went through I was trying to get
Chris in Chris had a little fun little experience
his truck it worked the other day I won't put them on blast or anything but
that tripped me out that looked just like the diesel that usually rolls by but it was not a diesel
fascinating um so my goodness it's a silly old world I you know what maybe maybe I'll go ahead and do
an early uh and brief producer segment and then we'll we'll get into the the nuts and bolts of the
of the show
yeah we'll do that um would like to thank everyone for hanging out being a part of a show uh this is
a value for value production
yes whenever I hear random music camp music fire up it will I will recall this exact spot
it's a value for value show if you're not familiar with the value for value system as pioneered by
the great folks at the no agenda podcast it's fairly straightforward each and every time you see
the show whether it's live during the summer monday through thursday now 7 a.m to 10 a.m
pacific or anywhere everywhere else you access it afterwards it will come to you for free
not going to put anything behind a paywall there's no if you subscribe here you get this and none of
that there's no advertisers sponsors um it's you if you see value in the show however much
that is whatever it is whatever it looks like to you send it this way and that's what allows for
the thing to continue
I've seen some proof of concept. It's you know the best thing that you could possibly ever do is share the show
That's how we get more eyes on it. That's how did we get to spread out the
Here's how the show works all that kind of stuff share links tell people about it
Good times
There's a couple of things outside of that that we could use a hand with that being time talent and treasure time and talent
There's only a couple of us trying to make the whole thing run everybody's got stuff going on
Everybody's stretched really thin and there's just not enough hours in the day or resources available to make it all run
So if you could help out on the time or talent and email the show a and wake up a proton male calm or Shelly
And wake up show comm send clips all that kind of stuff
You can help out on the treasure and
Multiple different ways for that all of the direct donate links are in the description of basically each in every video
Those are critical
Absolutely vital 100%
Did don't get anything done without them
There's also a link to the merch store you can now or will be sure it's soon available
Pre-order your 2024 year of the Marmot calendars
Sign up for the newsletter if you're anywhere near Sonoma County. You want to be a part of the monthly meet-ups
Gotta sign up for the newsletter. That's how you get the the deeds on
Where we're gonna be hanging out next this will be Sunday
July 23rd next meet-up
Details in Friday's newsletter
Yeah, and then we did have a couple of super a's
Let me recognize those people
Let's see Justice juice. Thank you very much putting a few bucks in the tech
Gremlin Jar is sir Peter Carther. Thank you very much Gregory Walker Steve
I think to sum up the federal government the state whatever you want to call these worthless cocksuckers
Big L says it best in the ghetto. You can only hope for a better tomorrow, but it only gets worse never better. Oh
Big L
Rest in peace
Yeah, all right guys, let's get back into
dead show
Let's see all kinds of stuff in the dock here
Where do I want to go?
Let's do let's talk about this a little bit
John brought it up a little bit of a
Discussion on exactly who
Elliot Abrams is but this is one of those things where now that this guy is back in the public sphere
officially employed as a public servant this
Partially animated
By a vindictive evil sorceress Jeff Dunham puppet looking
scumbag Elliot Abrams has a job in the Biden administration
Wow
Totally indefensible decision from Biden
Many Hassan of all people has said when many Hassan agrees with me
That this guy is a piece of shit
He's a real piece of shit. I think we talked about who was I talking about meddy with the other day?
I think it was Ryan, but yeah, I mean just how laughably
Terrible this fella is anyway
Um
Pointing to Abrams guilty plea stemming from the Reagan era
I ran contrast scandal in his broader record in Latin America. Well, you know, let's all just give a
brief moment pause to thank Bill Barr
for pardoning Elliot Abrams because he was attorney general at the time ultimately it was his decision
whether or not Abrams would
Would
Be convicted to anything and Bill Barr, of course
Came back during the Trump administration
and
People actually like that guy. They're the regular people walking around cheering on billy bar the the cover-up king Jason
Bermas would go off on it
extensively
time
Let's see
Most recently
Abrams served as Trump administration special envoy that ran in Venezuela during a 2019 house foreign affairs committee
hearing representative ill hand Omar
Grilled Abrams on his role in the Reagan administration's policy in El Salvador
It's us back military carried out the largest massacre in modern Latin American history in 1981 in and around the village
Velma's out there
Omar noted during 2019 hearing that Abrams later said the US policy in El Salvador was a
Fabulous achievement after recounting the appalling deaths of the El Mazote killings
Which around a hundred and forty children were murdered Omar asked Abrams
Do you think the massacre was a fabulous achievement happened under our watch? That's a ridiculous question
And I won't respond to it Abrams fumed in response
Not going to respond to that kind of personal attack, which is not a question
Abrams attempted to downplay the El Mazote massacre shortly after it occurred telling you a Senate that news reports of the gruesome killings
We're not credible. We're being misused by anti-government forces. It's the same line that they give you
when
When you talk about the reality of what's happening on the ground anywhere. Oh, well, that's going to but what do you want to give a
Gift of Vladimir Putin
Hey, did you know that there was another train derailment and our infrastructure is woefully inadequate. What do you do it?
You're just trying to prop up the Chinese
No, it's just I don't think we should be stealing money from Americans so that we can send it to a midget coke head
And why do you work for Vladimir Putin? I don't it just seems out of balance with what shut up
You tend foil hat wearing propagandist
Okay, um
And response to news of the Biden administration's decision to nominate Abrams to the State Department's advisory committee on public diplomacy
That's not a misprint
Long time former human rights watch executive director Kenneth Roth wrote that Abrams most notorious public diplomacy is downplaying
The 1991 El Mazote massacre of a thousand people by us trained and equipped Salvadoran military units
Raymond Bonner former New York Times correspondent in El Salvador wrote for the Atlantic in 2019 that the Reagan administration with Abrams as
Point man routinely defended the Salvadoran government in the face of evidence of its regular army and
Allied right-wing death squads were operating with impunity killing peasant students union leaders and anyone considered anti-government or pro guerrilla
Abrams went so far as to defend one of the death squads most notorious leaders Roberto
the Abusong
Obvis whatever responsible for the murder of Archbishop Oscar Romero while he was staying and
While he while he was saying mass in March 1980 you motherfucker
That's cold. That's cold
You want to kill a priest
While he's saying that that's someone who is not worried about any sort of afterlife consequences
The biden white house predictably failed to mention the sorted details of Abrams record and its nomination announcement offering a sterilized
Biography that lifts off the notorious figures previous government roles
assistant secretary of state for international organization affairs
Human rights in latin america under ronald reagan senior director of the national security council under george w bush
Special representative for iran special representative for venezuela under donald trump among others
okay
According to its website the advisory commission on public diplomacy is tasked with appraising u.s
government activities intended to understand informant influence foreign public's
And to increase the understanding of and support for these same activities
It's a
propaganda
office
It's the office of foreign propaganda
awesome
Slate journalist alex salmon denounced biden's
nomination of abram's from the position is obscene and unconscionable
elite abram's enemy of human rights
Apologist from ass murder should have no place within spitting distance of any democratic administration
In any capacity that does however
Suggest that abram's is apt to serve in republican administrations, which is a little bit of a false
paradigm there
I don't know
Oh, yeah, no, it's fine if he goes and you know destabilizes latin america and maskers people if a republicans in office
Fuck up slate journalist nobody likes you
Okay, uh, do you guys remember the the nexium cult?
And and how it sort of
Encapsulated a bunch of Hollywood a little sex trafficking thing that
Few years ago. There was a
Bronfman or two involved in it as well and
Allison Mack from Smallville
Well, she's been released from prison as a result of that or as a result of her or her affiliation
With the nexium cult
So Mack was sentenced to three years in 2021
After pleading guilty two years earlier to charges that she manipulated women and becoming sex slaves for nexium leader
Kenneth Rainier
Online records maintained by the federal bureau of privilege prisons said Mack was released from a federal prison in Dublin near that's Santa Rita
It's where commander X was
It plays a show by the way
Release Monday from Santa Rita
Mack avoided a longer prison term by
cooperating with federal authorities in their case against Rainier who was ultimately released from a federal prison in Dublin
Sentenced to 120 years in prison after being convicted on sex trafficking charges Mack helped prosecutors mount evidence
showing how Rainier created a secret society
That included brainwashed women who were branded with his initials forced to have sex with them
In addition to Mack members of the group included an heiress to the Seagram's liquor fortune Claire Bronfman
And a daughter of tv star Catherine oxenberg
Dynasty fame Mack would later repudiate Rainier and express remorse and guilt before her sentencing in federal court in Brooklyn, New York
They do give the the Claire Bronfman part. I believe her brother was also
connected to nexium
The Bronfman's of course
Figure in heavily into the Epstein saga
Going all the way back to the prohibition days
Formation of the American crime syndicate
At least as far as the sex trafficking for influence peddling and blackmail thing goes
That's the family business booze and sex trafficking
That's what you get from every bottle of sea grooms
Rose
Rose um, let's see
Um, there's all kinds of stuff in here
And it's gonna be kind of just haphazard. Oh, definitely
Definitely want to talk about this
Let me read it first reclaim the net
All right
Hello
You're pretty
Uh
So this is Rochelle Walensky y'all remember her she was the director of the cdc. She's uh
Primarily one of the main people responsible for gaslighting and fear mongering and selling the nation on mass experimentation
I don't know giving a whole bunch of people
As the cdc's director dr. Rochelle Walensky concludes her controversial tenure tenure
Her elevate revel Jesus fucking christ. You know what? I'm gonna try that again
I am
This is what happens when I only have one cup of coffee and one joint before the show
As the cdc's director dr. Rochelle Walensky concludes her controversial tenure
Her revelations about the agency's decision to work hand in glove with the media to shape public opinion raise alarming questions about government
overreaching the erosion of free speech
Now it does
Now it does in july of 2023 it does in real time when it was happening
We we were
Demonized for going. Hey, this is bullshit. But hey, you know, thanks appreciate it
In an interview with the wall street journal dr. Walensky did not meant words about her agency's attempts to shape the narrative
Concerning public health information through a process. She terms
pre-bunking
That and we did this on slow news day years ago. We pulled up the report
About pre-bunking this whole thing
Uh, there was a huge harvard study and harvard report that was
commissioned in order to do this and
Whatever. Anyway, this involved pre-emptive communication with media outlets to nudge them in a particular direction regarding health reports
ostensibly to curb
misinformation
But herein lies the crux of the issue who decides what constitutes misinformation
Closer look the cdc's performance during the covid-19 pandemic under dr. Walensky's stewardship reveals a troubling history
Of mixed messaging and reports that seemed influenced by political machinations the disturbing realization cdc's agenda was muddled by politics
Understandably eroded public trust dr. Walensky herself admitted to the agency's communication gaffes
That's neat we're gonna call
Bullshit and lies
out loud non-purpose
communication gaffes however
Revelation the cdc sought to shape the narrative by working with media outlets has been seen as deeply troubling from a free speech person
It should be seen as deeply troubling period not only from a free speech perspective
But from a hey, this is my health and my child's health that you're toying with
By lying to me every always about it that has less to do at free speech
And more to do with a death cult coming for your children
Zan
But yes, I agree reclaim the net that free speech is one of the cornerstones of a free society agreed
Yet the notion of a government agency engaging in pre bunking is eerily reminiscent of information policing
Yeah, it is collusion with media outlets further blurs the line between independent journalism and government propaganda
It erases it
Stark political partnership that enveloped walensky's term was highlighted by a kff study that revealed political affiliation as a significant
Predicator a predictor of kovat-19 vaccination. She pointed out that public health shouldn't be politicized yet
It is worrisome the agency under her watch
Arguably engaged in its own form of information
Politicking furthermore cdc's evolution under dr. Walensky is alarming brian castruci
The ceo of debaumat foundation
Rightly pointed out that cdc was once a somewhat obscure agency focused on advising health officials and conducting scientific studies
Now it's metamorphized
Into an institution with considerable public influence all while struggling with its new found role. Well, you put it in the movies
guys
You put it in the movies
Transparency and unbiased information are essential for individuals to make informed decisions
Dr. Walensky argued americans to fact-check information and consult trusted sources
The irony is stark. She speaks of trust her agency engaged in behind the scenes pre-bunking with media and suggests that the agency has a plan to
Continue it
right
She was investigated over the censorship demands placed on social media platforms, okay
Uh, this is a chance for reflection and recalibration
It's imperative for her successor dr. Mandy cohen
To address the fundamental issues of trust and transparency
Everybody show hands who believes that Mandy cohen is going to add trust and transparency to the cdc. That's what I thought
Yeah, yeah
Sure
Oh, shit. There's chris. Hell. Yeah. Well, you guys I'm gonna let chris from the rained out rancas to explain why he's not at work today
It's definitely not my my job
Uh, but always a pleasure to uh, to have him join the stream here. Y'all uh, what's happening chris? How you doing my friend?
What's going on? Can you hear me? Yes, sir?
Fantastic shirt. Um
Yeah, I uh
Someone should do it anyways. Uh, yeah, I I'm on the show today because it's it is actually raining
but
Uh, I was fired
I I always preferred that the phrase invited to become successful elsewhere
Yeah, uh pretty much, uh, I have to look for success in podcasting now
Uh, I just started a new show called rained out rancas
Yeah, now I gotta I had a little incident at work. So I'm I'm off for a while until the next
to work. You talking about the censorship thing going on? Yeah, I was just taking a look at some
of that. Well, because the Walensky, the former CDC director, like now that she's leaving and can't
really be held accountable for anything, they're disclosing and more... She's a liar. Yeah,
she was colluding with media outlets in order to set a predetermined narrative about products that
turns out they knew were not just ineffective, but would actually harm people.
Yeah, and you see that social media lawsuit that's going on that a judge, I'm sure you've
talked about it, the judge put a stop to them using social media to censor us.
Well, I didn't do a show yesterday. It was in the doc and it's in the doc.
Oh yeah, they just came out. Yeah, because that all goes with this, because that's what they were
using it for. And then now the Biden administration is appealing that ruling, you know, because they
don't want to give up that power. It's fucking crazy because that Missouri lawsuit I thought had
pretty much got thrown out months ago, but apparently not. It is still going through.
Yeah, there's parts of it that are allowed to go through and parts of it that they weren't
from the best of my under from my reading of it. I do have the
CBS here, but yeah, Terry Doherty of Louisiana granted the injunction in a response to a 2022
lawsuit brought by attorneys in Louisiana, Missouri, substantial evidence of far reaching
censorship campaign and almost dystopian scenario. Well, yeah, I mean, we know that we live through it,
but reviewing the injunction will evaluate its option. The administration has promoted
responsible actions to protect public health safety and security when confronted
by challenges like a deadly pandemic and foreign attacks on our elections. Jesus Christ, dude.
That's hacky. What's crazy is I seen the New York Times released an article on this
saying the case was brought by brought by two Republican attorney generals
and five individuals who campaigned against masks argued that vaccine did not vaccines did not
work oppose lockdowns and push drugs that medical experts denounced as ineffective like
ivermectin and a hydroxychloroquine. And it it is being overseen by Judge Terry A. Doherty,
who I think I pronounced that right, who was appointed by President Donald J. Trump and has
previously expressed little skeptic skepticism about debunked claims from vaccine skeptics.
In one previous case, Judge Doherty accepted as fact the claim that COVID-19, they got this in
quotes, COVID-19 vaccines do not prevent transmission and disease. Yeah, because they said that it
doesn't like what the fuck they're trying to say this guy is a fucking Nazi because he cited
the very thing that they first they said they didn't say and then they said we did say and
then when I go look back at it because I got all I pretty much have every video of them talking
about the efficacy and yeah it went from $199.98 and there's the montages and shit. But then
to say that this judge because all it is a Psyop it's just this manipulation of the mind
and trying to like like what they're doing with Trump you know they're trying to
attain a jury pool basically but the majority of jury pools of cases like that are going to be
pulled from Cambridge right a lot of people forgot about Cambridge Analytica you know and
there's talk that that's where Roger Stone's jury came from was pulled from Cambridge because
they'd be able to pull it they they already stated they could pull a jury that would sway
one way or the other just with the Cambridge Analytica yeah which is when Facebook stole
all of our shit remember yep they didn't really steal it they had already stole it we gave it to
them all and then they soft disclosed to us that they stole it and then they blamed it on this other
people and then you are there you seen it yes sir yes sir dude it's like the cocaine in the White
House right first this is crazy because Sunday night is when it came across I started posting
about it Sunday night Twitter is a piece of shit now you know mobile yeah I'm talking like it's
it's use not that you know just the use of it this is really piece it's pissing me off now
because I'm trying to look at shit on the mobile and then I respond to it and my shit just crashes
and doesn't fucking work and I gotta do it on anyways the Twitter with the cocaine thing
right when that started going off had the police scanner within a couple hours of that
right and it states in there you know it was found in the library they thought it was heroin
they thought it was an opioid and it tests positive for cocaine hydrochloride which cocaine
hydrochloride is crack um well okay so cocaine hydrochloride is like the pure shit
it when you cook it it's like it turns into like cocaine hydroxide or something like
they're the best hydroxide to the best of my understanding when you add the baking soda to
it it becomes hydroxide it when it's the high because hydrochloric acid is what if you if you're
manufacturing cocaine you've got mashed up coca leaf and then initially what i'm writing this down
man pour a you pour like a wash of hydrochloric acid over it and that's what makes it like cake up
okay and then i'm not sure they just found good coke they found good coke i thought uh
uh i guess that makes sense crack out what what they found was ambassador grade cocaine
the they didn't find street level cocaine then it would have tested positive for fentanyl too
and they would have said that or they would have straight up said like i don't know if they
can be like yeah we found crack at the white house okay is that why they because you know
coke does work to numb teeth pain and stuff it definitely numbs the throat when you snore it's
a local anesthetic basically yeah i don't know who uses the like do doctors don't use
that as a local anesthetic anymore no so the when they first reported this the first
mainstream that did drop something about it they put in that they found cocaine hydrochloride
is that my saying that right yeah and uh that that is what's used sometimes for a local anesthetic
yeah yeah because that's where the hydrochloric well okay once upon a time it is what they mean
in the same way that like you know heroin used to be in cough syrup yes but that's the
gaslighting shit because the first official report states it's something used as a local
anesthetic because when you put the cocaine hydrochloride now it's a scientific type thing
and it's not just some coke or crack it's fucking cocaine hydrochloride that's that's
something i don't know they know who's coke it is they know who's coke it is well on the
dispatch you hear the cop tell the other one wipe the bags down there's two of them it seems
like there's two of them because he says i mean i could play it i can yeah pull it yeah pull it up
let's do that the one i have is like five minutes i don't get it's a fucking we got another hour and
a half buddy all right yeah let's listen to the whole fucking thing then let me pull it
live my grab we'll fucking do it live oh i'm way off on that we'll do it live fucking do it
live i um shit now my instagram probably won't let me in anyways he said uh it's not gonna do it
it's not it's seriously gonna kick me out yep all the social medias are i feel like there's
gonna be like this purge like uh i feel like twitter's gonna purge anybody who's not paying on the
mobile mm-hmm they're gonna leave the pc because nobody uses pc you know because if you notice
pc there's seems there's no fucking problem with the pc version yeah you can you know let me see if
this one let me in yeah no and i'm checking too because i'm pretty sure you put a link to it and
one of the group shots that we're on yeah i have a couple clips oh my god they did they're not
letting me in the uh you fucking assholes you you're booted from instagram i don't know what's
going on it won't let me in i know that did it let me in now nope okay anyways i can pull it up
off my phone but so anyways they find it and it seems like they found it in two different places
the one spot
was like inaudible what he says but then the second spot is the library I mean
he clearly says the library and then they said then another report comes out
and says oh it was in a cubby where people put their cell phones first it
was in the West Wing where nobody goes and then it was like oh it's a
heavily trafficked area the story just keeps changing and changing and
I mean could you imagine going on vacation and getting to where you're
going with your goddamn pedo fucking father and all the shit that's going on
you ain't you fucking lost your cocaine and fucking you don't have your laptop
and shit I mean it's it's got to be it's got to be stressful I don't know who you
you probably send a secret service to get more I don't know how that works
I'm not a I mean look yeah the the White House has an in-building or
Congress at least has an in-building pharmacy there's a pharmacy in the basement
or everything they need in there right so yeah I mean you could theoretically just
order up your local anesthetic from the pharmacy even if you look man I was
just talking about this with John you know half an hour or so ago but I mean
dude I lived around DC hung out there quite a bit it did it caffeine and cocaine
make the town run that's just that that's the simple fact of it so that's what
makes this to me such a fucking non-story oh you found cocaine and
Washington DC I'm just over here fucking stunned bro I am so it's like
what it seems like such a distraction because it's ongoing it won't well they
have their own hazmat there was no call that needed to be made to the metro the
DC Metro PD or whatever there was no outside call that had to be made Alex
Jones made that point that which I was saying to my buddy when I was texting
he voted for Biden I was texting look now there's fucking coke in the fucking
thing these fucking secret service they didn't have to call anybody no and they
fucking called so it was on the let me pull this up I got this ready that's
what I'm saying they want that on record yep and like Jones he's like it's a
call for help I don't know about that but no it's it's fucking it's you know it's
not only a distraction but it is like who's is it you're never gonna find out
who's is it because cameras probably weren't working at the time to say it's
so heavily trafficked how you're gonna fucking know who you know how do you
even get in with it in your pocket are you not searched at the you know
like what not not like that because if you've got a staff-led tour or if you're
an invited guest to the the West Wing specifically then you know chances are
like what you're you're wanted you may even be like lightly patted down but
this is a public place is a public part of the the White House you do get you
know like scheduled routine guided tours through it so the it's the whatever
surveillance that they have plus you getting wanded and then you have to give
up your cell phone you basically got to empty your pockets if you're going into
a secure area or something like that but that's what they have logs of
everybody that's in and out of that oh yeah yeah yeah no they know exactly
who's blow it was that 100 and they've known it since two hours after they
made it a story we listen to a little bit of this because there's a part in it
where he fucking tells him to wipe the baggies down I think it's after they
find out it's cold can you hear that barely really god damn I've got it
pretty well boosted over here let me see if I can change that
still hard to hear yeah I mean it's a police scanner the second voice is
clear okay have you completed an art kit he's there going back and forth they're
running an art kit because they first thought it was opioids now they're running
this Gemini system that analyzes and I guess it takes like 10 minutes to run
it they have to run it twice that's how good this blow is fucks up the Gemini
it's price on Clinton blow that was the the joke I made on our big dumb mouth last
night being offered the Roger Clinton tour
oh shit okay so the Narcan what yeah so the Narcan I thought it had shown a
negative but he said it showed a positive for the possibility then they move into
that Gemini hmm see I don't nobody has put the scanner completely together you
know just those pieces because even on the screen there you can see like the 25
next that encrypted it these are the ones that are like if you go over if I had
more of the screen showing it would show like how many likes this that star
right there has yeah and it's like a couple hundred just on these two
encrypted ones and then the rest nobody's listening to
the entry make sure you take a picture of the results on that marked it
and I'm back that up separately
has meant to entry because we're backing up the North Kits separately from
everything else
also currently reading that product are 20.982 zero in the other country three
you are and three minutes left on the go now that's my okay good one
I didn't copy repeat coffee one minute one
jim and i
uh...
to repeat i didn't have your results on the jim and i
here's where he's uh... pretty sure he states the two spots
jim and i's results are jim and i found
with the red bar
jim and i found it in the library
we'll go ahead and write it, come on up
one was found in the red something
and then the other the library
he states
two spots
could you hear that on there?
to repeat i didn't have your results on the jim and i
listen
jim and i's results are jim and i found
with the red bar
jim and i found it in the library
we'll go ahead and write it, come on up
sounds like two different spots
yeah but the library
i mean that's uh...
that's very audible on there
yeah, run that test one more time with the jim and i please
just reposition the laser
you got the 908s with the park
312s upon oklahoma station track one
i didn't copy or repeat
negative we did not have the 908s
the question is, we have a
result on the jim and i
We have a yellow bar, stating cocaine, hydrochloride, gas number, 5-3, that's 2-1, that's 4.
Okay.
Are we still wishing these in I-0-8 or was I going to bag it up?
Bag it up separately.
Don't worry about the I-0-8.
When you guys come out, we're made on air.
Then we're going to have engine 23 wiped it out.
Also, we're going to have some R-DK wipes.
Go ahead and wipe those down.
Wipe your hands first and then wipe the bags down, please.
Wipe the bags down.
I don't know if that's procedure or what.
So...
Thank you, man.
Yeah, before you shut the Gemini off, make sure you take a picture of that screen, please.
Yeah, coffee, though. We've got to go, folks.
I didn't copy. Can you repeat?
Thank you.
Wild.
What the fuck? How do I stop that?
Oh, there we go.
Yeah, so...
I mean, how many fucking tours were they given and shit?
They'll never know who fucking...
Because it's a federal offense. It's felony.
Yeah.
It's another felony.
If it's Hunter's shit...
He's like his gun charge.
I don't think has been...
like even done with yet, right?
There's a plea that there's a different thing going to go on with the gun charge.
That he's not going to get 10 years for it, for sure.
So...
Well, here's the thing about people acting like it might be Hunter Biden's cocaine.
Hunter doesn't go into the West Wing Library from the visitor's entrance.
That's like one of the starting points of a tour is the West Wing Library.
Hunter comes from the residence side of it.
So his shit wouldn't be in that cubby to begin with,
because that's just not the way that he would go in.
He would already be inside from a different entrance, from a different, you know...
But was it in the cubby?
Because the first reports was that something was found outside.
That it was found in a storage room.
No, that was bullshit because, okay, there was...
What that was was a bunch of social media accounts
that did see that the hazmat unit had been called out
but kept recirculating a picture from, like, 2018.
As, oh, they're outside the building!
And it was the two guys in front of the fence that are fucking...
Or, like, behind the fence.
You see the picture taken from behind the fence.
So the fence is in the foreground, and there's two guys in hazmat suits.
That's an old-ass picture that people were, like, hypersensationalizing
because they didn't have any real information, so they were using that picture.
And that's where it got that it was outside of the building.
As far as I can tell.
And then, like, a half an hour later, we started getting more reports
that were, like, okay, well, they found something that they say is coke in the West Wing.
And that's where all the Hunter Biden stuff started coming from.
As soon as it was confirmed that it was West Wing,
a bunch of people ran with the idea that it was somehow Hunter's fucking blow.
And, look, let's be honest.
Somebody at that level of crackhead, even if you lose your laptop,
you know where your drugs are.
You do. You know where your drugs are.
So it might be the only thing that you can locate at any given point
is your stem and your freaking, you know, your bag
or your vial or whatever you're holding it in.
If you're Hunter Biden, you're not finding your pants, that's for sure.
You don't care what those are.
Yeah, I didn't know about the West Wing part until, what, like Monday
or maybe Monday afternoon or something that it was in the West Wing itself.
But the, yeah.
I mean, who was it in the storage box, though?
So, okay, I just had John on.
And I don't know, I can't confirm whether or not he's 100% accurate.
But according to him, and he's got a significant amount of beltway contacts,
it was, according to him, like somebody took out their cell phone
threw it in the cubby and the bag was pinched on a little bit of the case
or whatever. And then when they pulled their cell phone out,
it had, you know, the bag had dislodged or it was static to it
and then wasn't or what, and then that's where they found it.
Now, I don't, I can't say with 100% certainty that that's the accurate story,
but that's the story that we just got told by the DC Insider guy.
Well, I don't know, I don't, but I don't know.
I don't know.
Cause he still has funny opinions.
I was hopping earlier, or watching earlier.
He's still, you know.
Yeah, it's just, it's funny that, like, again, they didn't need to call hazmat,
they didn't need to call it outside nothing.
So it's like this, it's like when they flew the flag upside down.
Mm-hmm.
You know, they flew that flag upside down for what, like 30 minutes or some shit?
Yeah.
That's not an accident.
Right?
No.
No, that's something that you spot instantly as it's going up,
where somebody radiates it.
I think as you're fucking clipping it on.
Unfurling it.
Yeah, you noticed that pretty much straight away.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Yeah, so it's a, it's a while.
My, uh, have you, they finally asked KJP had an opportunity to-
I haven't watched the whole thing of this yet.
That's true about the Coke.
Oh, it's, it's fantastic.
Hang on.
I think I recorded it.
We're exactly inside the West Wing.
I mean, the substance was discovered.
I'm not going to get into specifics.
All I can say is when people visit the West Wing,
there is an air, there is the area of the West Wing where it is highly
traveled.
And that is what happens.
People come through this particular area, it's highly traveled.
I'm just not going to get into specifics.
I'm not going to get into, uh, not going to get ahead of the
Secret Service.
And so I'll let them speak to that.
There are a couple of primary entrances into the West Wing.
There's the one with which we're all familiar right outside of
the driveway where the Marine stands and the President's in the
West Wing.
And there's another entrance of West Executive Avenue.
Can you explain which, which entrance we're talking about?
I'm going to let the Secret Service speak to that.
Can you explain why you can't explain it?
I mean, you can describe it as a heavily traveled area.
That's what the secret, I'm just saying what the Secret Service
said.
We got this from the Secret Service.
So I'm sharing a little bit more with you from here.
But again, it's under their purview.
It's under investigation.
They will, they will have more specifics down the road as
they are looking into this.
We are confident that they will get to the bottom of this.
And so I'm just going to leave it to them.
Something was discovered late on Sunday.
What's the latest staff-led tours that happen in the
West Wing on Sunday?
You know, I don't have the specific on how late the staff
tours, staff-led tours go.
But I can tell you that there was one on Friday.
There was one on Saturday.
It was on one on Sunday.
The times that there are not any West Wing tours is when
there is a federal holiday like yesterday or a big White House,
a large White House event.
I just don't have the specifics.
Let's, let's let the Secret Service get to the bottom of this.
They'll have more, hopefully more information and we have
confident that they will be able to figure this all out.
So I'm going to give them the space to do that.
When were tours even started back up, you know, with COVID
after lockdown?
I would have had to have been fairly recently, right?
Didn't the White House just clear everyone for takeoff
in like mid-May?
Yeah, but then at the same time, I mean, they're still pushing
this COVID narrative.
So because they had, well, the NCAA or some high,
some kids there, some school where the not unvaccinated
had to wear masks.
This was just like a couple of weeks ago.
Yeah, yeah.
So I wonder when the tour started.
Now, this has got me to think like the balloon situation,
right?
These things they create.
So then the speculation, so that way they can come
and go, look, we found who it was.
It definitely wasn't Hunter.
You guys are all fucking.
And then they laugh and then they run away.
Well, that's I mean, you would want the narrative
that that it's hunters blow to proliferate just so you
could come back.
They know exactly who's I mean, come on, dude.
Yeah, this is like the plane hitting the Pentagon.
Yeah.
Like, where's the fucking video?
But you can't get video.
It's inside a box.
You don't know who the fucks it is.
It's just to create rampant speculation.
They did not need to call anybody at all.
This did not need to go over the air at all.
Like, let's see a picture of this baggie a blow.
Is it like a fucking?
It's just a little corner.
It's just that little corner shit.
So I'm going to be DM last night with the mic had
some audio from a report and they.
described it as like a dime bag in 2023.
Somebody on the news used the expression dime bag or size of a dime or something like that.
OK, I mean, a dime of coke.
I'm not a powder person, so I don't I don't know what a fucking dime of coke is.
It sounds like a nice, fat rail.
It sounds like a good way to start the night.
I don't I don't know, man.
I never did rails.
I just stick my straw in the bag.
Yeah, that's that's baller.
I mean, but this then, yeah.
Yeah, I'm going to take a quick detour here.
All right. Go down memory lane.
We're talking about a family friend
and her love of cocaine back back in the day.
Day. And there was like there was a game that these motherfuckers would play
on the Santa Cruz Beach where they were all longboard enthusiasts,
right, when that sort of broke and they would take they'd fucking
kind of wipe down the deck on the bottom side and in between trucks
would line out rails and then they'd go on either side of it
head to head, literally and have races.
Sweet. Yeah, that much code.
That is that is a that's a freaking
lifestyle choice for sure.
I'm not a big coke person.
I I I've done it.
Multiple times, but I have always preferred to be like down
as opposed to up where the drugs are concerned.
I never found coke to even get me up, you know.
It's almost the opposite
if you're thinking about things getting up, but that's true.
That's true. It does that one of you just make me think I was choking
to death, you know, because I couldn't feel my throat.
And then you'd be hanging out and then that coke would drop
from your nasal passage and your throat again.
You throw up like, whoa.
That was good. Yeah. Yeah.
That's basically it. I mean, you got to hear your idiot friend
rattle off his 450 terrible business ideas.
Yeah. Which, you know, I mean, it's a trope, but it does happen.
I'm from Iowa.
So it was a big it's a big meth place.
Coke is the rich man's shit, you know, and meth is.
But whenever I had Coke, I would, you know,
I just stick my fucking straw in the bag because I didn't think
it would do anything.
So we do, you know, if you did these big lines and shit,
it all did numb your throat.
So I'm like, let's just fucking get as much as I can get in here.
You know, because you can do a line and you still got you could keep going.
But the line's gone and you could you could just keep snorting.
Why not just, you know, go to the source.
Right right from the bag.
Yeah, it's fair, fair.
And I mean, look to that's I mean,
that's kind of the same basic principle as the bullet, right?
The bullet, the cocaine bullet.
What's that?
You're not familiar with this device?
I'm not. I'm not OK, you know.
OK, well, I don't know.
I didn't know how.
You put it up your butt or something.
I didn't know how far into culture.
The bullet had gone.
No. No. No. No.
it holds about a tiner, half an eight ball, right. And it is. It's a bullet-shaped device
and you twist it upside down and you kind of turn it a little bit and it activates our glass-like
filling up a part of the, you know, bullet-shaped tip with the cocaine. And then you close it
and you flip it over and it's got a nice little duty-toot for you right there. It's fairly,
fairly conceivable, fairly low-key. Get those on Amazon. I'm sure you could. I'm sure.
They're probably part of the Joe Biden Here Have a Better Life kit with the crack pipe and all
of that other stuff. We wouldn't want you to go out there, you know, under supplied.
Free Coke bullets.
That's part of the gun buyback program. It's part of the gun buyback program now. We're going to
give you free cocaine bullets so that you stop shooting real ones. Yeah, because you can't put
the two together because then we have to take you to jail. Right. But if you separate, unless
you're Hunter Biden and then, I mean, these precedents that have been set, you know,
in front of us is ridiculous. It's pretty crazy, dude. It's pretty crazy. I want to go through and
make a list of these precedents that we've seen over the last like eight years or so, you know,
and even like these precedents when it comes like Trump and the DOJ, the DOJ, which overstepping,
it's more of disclosure shit, you know? I mean, we knew what they were doing and then it's
it's just like disclosure. Yeah, we were doing it. Understanding of co Intel pro has figured this out,
but there are still a lot of people who don't even know about that. So I did there. Yeah,
Dave Chappelle mentions co Intel pro in a bit that's like, I don't know, probably seven or eight
years old now. And I can remember very clearly, people that I grew up with and stuff like that,
getting a hold of me after that special drop going, you know about this thing, right? What's the
the problem? You know, okay, well, because Dave said it, you know about it now groovy, groovy.
Yeah, we can talk. Yeah. Yeah. And like, people are posting about like France being able to
turn on phones and in all that shit in America, that's like the telecommunications act of 1996,
I believe signed by Bill Clinton gave the ability to turn on and off devices. At the time,
we did have some sort of flippy fucking cell phone thing. And in there, I mean, it's supposed
to be to where you can flip those on and off without a battery, they have to be able to be
for emergencies. 911 location, we got to find you. So we got to be I mean, if the batteries
that we got to be able to find you. So yeah, I mean, people are freaking out about France. And
meanwhile, I mean, that shit was already put into place fucking
to almost 20, what 30 years ago. Yeah. Yeah. And there are a couple of people,
well, a number of people in Congress and in government that were instrumental in crafting
that legislation that are still running around, still part of all everything fucking legacy shit.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. The and the Kennedy family instrumental in shaping that legislation from
behind the scenes to I posted a picture of the old RFKJ, you know, because he was doing an interview
with Megan Kelly last year, I think, you know, he's always in front of his bookshelf. And I notice
on this interview, the fucking swastika, I don't know what book it is. And then the Hitler's
generals and I just made a made his face funny and circled those I didn't put any commentary
or anything. I don't think I just posted it. And people are like, what's that supposed
to mean? People can't read about Nazis and shit. And it's like, if it was Bill Gates or someone,
you'd fucking retweet it, you know, like, yeah, I didn't even say anything. I'm not,
I just put it, I thought it was funny. And it's just the way it stuck out the swastika.
I don't know what book it is. Might be mine, Com. Because I mean, it is the
Kurt Master pointed out the other day, the other week, that everybody who runs for president now
has to write their mind comp first. And it's like they've all got a book, they all go and
promote their book tour. And it's always literally, this is my struggle. And now I'm here. It
dreams from my father, whatever the fuck you want to title it, but it's always my struggle.
And then they put their mind comp out. And then they get thrust into, you know, a higher tier
in the public spotlight. People have to read though. Well, I mean, look at how many copies
the real Anthony Fauci sold, rightfully so. Honestly, I mean, somebody needed to write
that book. You know, I don't have any problem with RFK Junior, the author or the, you know,
whatever is active, any sphere of his activism, I know a lot of it rubs up against the NGO
industrial complex, and it's incredibly shady. But it's, he's a Kennedy, I get that that's
going to happen. I don't even fault him for that shit. It seems like a vanity campaign,
unless he's being elevated to that position. Yeah, I don't know what to make of the dude.
Like, I find out more and more, like, I didn't know a second, his second, I didn't,
I don't know a whole shitload about RFK there, you know, but he's been
married three times a second wife fucking killed herself.
It's like, damn, nobody mentioned that?
Like I had to hear him tell Jim Burr that?
Nobody mentioned that because there's been
a coordinated media campaign on behalf of the Kennedy family
to ever talk about it.
And if you do, you have to demonize this bitch
because she was a reckless drunk
who needed to have her kids taken away
who needed to have Bobby and his side chick
who was his now wife move in like a couple hundred yards
away across the street.
Yeah.
Oh, like the psychological warfare
that was conducted on this lady.
And I'm not saying she was a saint
by any stretch of the imagination.
I'm not trying to, you know,
this is the shit that we know.
But I mean that the whole family like engaged
in full on psychological warfare against this woman
that her smeared in the press after her death
went to work on her corpse and memory.
Like it was wild dude.
So that's why you don't hear a lot about it.
But even then, like it's all, they're gonna,
if he starts pulling above 30%,
they're gonna pull out all of the stops
and you will hear every lurid Kennedy detail
from all sorts of, you know, unauthorized sources
or whatever, it'll be insane.
It'll be gross.
And then you'll have people defending
even the worst of the real shit
because the smears are so bad.
Yeah.
I again, Kennedy's, I know, you know,
JFK CIA, RFK, you know,
I haven't dug way deep in the RFK.
It's just, I watched a little bit of his interviews
and shit, you know, with like Bill Maher
and like, I mean, he talks a good game.
Yeah. You know, what they all do.
Well, apparently, according to Scott Horton anyway,
and I don't think, you know, I don't think Horton
is talking out of his ass when he says this,
but the little Bobby was at pork fest
saying all of the right things
about the second amendment.
And then he turns around and does that town hall thing
where he's like, oh yeah, it absolutely signed
bipartisan legislation, the bank guns, you know,
which I understand is a political answer
because he knows he's never gonna get bipartisan support
for that, I understand that.
But what you're still doing is you're tailoring
your message to them.
You're populist.
Well, you're fucking, you're a politician
doing 100% politician shit, which is supposed to be
something that cancels you out for the vast majority
of the, at least the independent media
that's been talking them up and, you know,
throwing their support behind them and stuff like that.
Normally, when somebody behaves exactly like a politician,
it's supposed to raise some red flags and go,
oh, well, this guy is going to say whatever.
And then when he gets in, he's gonna do whatever
they tell him because that's what politicians do.
But no, this time is different.
This time, this time, guys, like, I don't know.
Like I said, I watched a little bit of the Jim Brewer thing
found out his wife murdered herself.
Or maybe she will, I don't know how she died.
Right.
Cause I didn't look into it yet,
but I have time now to actually look,
start digging into more shit again, cause, you know,
I'm fired.
Right, there's that, there's that.
Can you get some, can you file for some Biden bucks?
Can Bidenomics go to work for you?
We collect unemployment?
No.
The only way that Bidenomics works for anybody?
Nah, I wouldn't get none anyways.
I'll be back to work probably next week.
Just right now it sucks.
Was not, it was very unexpected.
I tipped my truck over.
Yeah.
Yeah, the load got stuck at the top of my dump truck.
That's going to say.
And it fucking gravity.
If that's what you call it, took over.
And it, yeah.
After almost a decade of a perfect fucking record,
I fucking dumped a truck.
Well, anyways, so, bro, I, okay, so.
That was a weird segue.
We went from RFK's wife fucking killing herself to somebody else's
dump load.
Oh, yeah, I was fucking murdered myself.
Fucked up.
Dude, my, I had a buddy whose name was also Chris, ironically,
was a driver for San Lorenzo Lumber back in the day.
Oh, shit.
Was coming down highway 17 and the load shifted to the right.
And he just, I mean, just, and it wasn't even really that he even took the corner
too hot.
It was just, it was that severe of a corner.
And I don't, you know, I don't know if he had a slower reaction time or whatever.
But load shifted.
It went, he went.
Highway patrol pulls up, first of all, with like a what the fuck is going on here.
Mara proceeds to just unload on this cop.
Every little thing that's wrong with his life.
OK, and by the time he's done bitching, like the hypo was starting to feel really,
really bad for him.
And he's like, OK, buddy, here's what's going to happen.
You know, like I got it.
I have to call some of this and blah, blah, blah, blah, try and take care of you.
Holy shit.
I hope you, you know, I hope you don't get fired because according to you,
nobody wants your wife to really find out about this.
Like, it was, it was hilarious.
Fucking nobody even checked on me.
They were like, they just walked away.
Then I. Yeah, this was hard to miss.
It was it was in the middle of Highway 17 and between San Jose and Santa Cruz,
like the only major highway in between the two at a point where the road
narrows quite a bit.
Yeah. See, I wasn't on the road.
I was I was on a job site, so it makes a big fucking difference.
I wasn't moving. I wasn't, you know, so it makes a huge difference.
It's still my pride hurts.
Yeah, my truck.
Oh, man, I got close one time, one time.
Didn't there's been a lot of times.
Didn't actually go to two pallets of landscape blocks in the back of this truck.
And I mean, it was a bit, you know, the dump ad truck, it was built for it.
But I'm trying to drive Highway nine in Santa Cruz, which is very, very windy.
And even though I'm going like 25, 30, every little bit of shift was full pucker.
Yeah. See, I got to drive through like the Boston mountains
and the Ozark mountains and shit.
So it's very everywhere I go is a fucking twist.
Turn fucking nightmare uphill, downhill, uphill, downhill.
I mean, when I first started doing this, I had a CDL, you know,
but I'd never actually driven a fucking truck.
I had been driving an automatic.
And they're like, can you drive this fuck? Yeah, it's like a car.
It's not, though. They're not like cars.
No, they're not. They're nothing like cars.
I broke a fucking shaft once going uphill
when I'd first started doing this.
So we're like in a convoy and this old man missed his gear in front of me.
They had just done my breaks.
And when I fucking had my was holding trying to hold myself up the hill,
I start rolling backwards.
I panicked and I fucking went down in the fucking low
and come off the clutch and snap the fucking drive shaft in half
because I was loaded.
Yeah. But you see some of the dump trucks on the road here
that are driving these quick twisty turn.
Oh, my God, they're like death traps, man.
I happened to a buddy that I did a bunch of bunch of jobs with stuff
like that over the years guy was in my phone forever to shoot myself
in the foot, Josh, because he did.
I've told that story a couple of times again,
but shot himself with a roofing gun, like getting up onto the dumb ass.
But yeah, overloaded his truck all the time, all the time.
One day we're rolling away from a job site.
And oh, my God, dude, the not just the drive shaft,
but like the pumpkin and the transfer case just bloated.
I mean, like shrapneled out for yards.
It was hectic.
It's yeah, and it's like I did it up on a hill
and everybody you went around me now, I got to figure out.
how to get I'm slowly coming down the hill because my brakes ain't holding so I just I have no
no gear so nothing to slow me except the brakes so I just let it go and I fucking come rolling down
and I turn and I parked on this this shoulder when dude got there he's like how the fuck did
you get it here from there and I was like I just backed it down I just let it you know
yeah because them hills loaded with no engine to do the work and you're just trying to use your
brakes oh my god it's that's scary shit if anybody's retarded enough to do that yeah don't do that
like I'll lead I'll lead trucks through these crazy twists and turns and my brake lights don't
come on much you know what I'm in a manual when I'm in a standard and because I'm just using
the truck to letting it do all the work you know these guys will come down their brakes are fucking
smoking and shit it's like your brake lights didn't even come on it's like they really shouldn't that
much I mean they really shouldn't you'd let the truck do the work you let the motor do the work
it's the same way I ride my bike yeah let it do the work let it do the slowing down and shit
plus it's louder right well yeah trying to teach uh trying to teach my my oldest
mountain driving and stuff like that and it's just something I can't stress enough do you gotta you
know so you're in the mountain gears for a reason it has gears for a reason you're up there in the
mountain mountains right like when I say like Boston mountains Ozark mountains to me they seem
like hills I mean they are pretty high hills and twist and in turn and but like they call them mountains
but I always think of like snow cap shit you know like mountain mountains you know huge ridges
so here it's a little bit too close to the coast to be snow capped where where my kid's mom lives
that's Yosemite in the Sierra foothills and all that kind of stuff like those are mountain
mountains here there's you know anywhere from like 900 to 16 1700 feet but it goes from sea level
vertically up several hundred feet more or less immediately and so you know there's plenty of spots
where on one side of you is you know rock and then on the other side of you is nothing it's
just a cliff and then whatever trees would catch you and they're you know a couple hundred foot
redwood yeah so it's a long way down but but it's not like oh I'm plummeting 13 000 feet to the bottom
of yeah that's kind of what it is here I mean I think the tallest peak is mount magazine it's
like 1500 feet or something but there's spots where you're riding you got the cutoffs of the
granite and then to the other side of you there's some trees they're gonna catch you
it's gonna fucking hurt ashley's ashley's family property that we're gonna start cleaning out and
rebuilding and building on and stuff like that and we'll be documenting all that it's the highest point
in five miles is it yeah that'd be dope yeah that'd be dope see driving around here I've been to
like all these amazing sites you know where things are being built houses are being built
and it was last year I went to this one place that like blew me away like it was the greatest site I'd
ever seen like you have to go through like the mark twain forest so like you turn off the main highway
and for like three quarters of a mile there's a couple little houses a trailer you can see the
power lines you know and then there's this dense trees and the road goes through at the power
line stop and then you go in like another mile and I'm going through this with a load and I'm
like what the fuck there's no there's no way there's anything out here like I've I've got to be down
the road the GPS definitely led me the wrong fucking place and I'm going down this I can't even see
through the trees it's so fucking dense go through this fence boom it's like 700 acres this guy has
cleared off for 20 years cut the top of that mount the end of that mountain off it's except
for right where he came from it's what would it be 300 degree fucking views all as far as you
can see just amazing and all he has is this little house has to have a water tower up there
and shitty as no I don't even think they have power up there yeah yeah yeah that'd be dope
that's dude that I'll yeah I think I did I think I sent you a couple of pictures of this spot
yeah it's 100% what like you know I mean your background is pretty sweet well and this is
residential where I am technically yeah I was gonna I was thinking about taking the laptop out
and trying to match my background to it but I thought it was actually raining yeah I gotta tell
you man I as much as it was nice to have the the amenities of a studio I am so fucking much
more happy and comfortable being back outside on and when it does start raining this fall I'm gonna
try and set up an enclosure on the other side of the porch door it won't be super loud but I can still
be at least you know half ass outside while I do it because it's just yeah I'm working outside my
whole life I don't like being indoors much anyway yeah it's fucking it's dope the outside
podcast there's a hummingbird like eight feet away right now yeah I mean it is I get interrupted by
chickens I am I ain't even mad yeah especially digs fucking giving us like seven eggs a day
that's good fuck yeah I'll take that um switching gears like a lot this is freaking hysterical
uh the reality finds a way to rub up against even the best narratives
you know like so eventually reality is gonna creep in and the the result of that is Democrat
Senator Chris Murphy taking some heat for saying that we can't avoid the biological differences
between men and women fucking right winger right this Nazi Democratic Connecticut Senator
Chris Murphy seemingly broke with party orthodoxy Sunday when he acknowledged that men and women
are different Murphy now on twitter he just finished reading Richard Reeves 2022 book of boys
and men in which the author details the struggles modern-day males are facing having read the
book senator concluded the left is missing the crisis happening with men today and that biological
and evolutionary differences between men and women can't be avoided that's that's a super bold
statement coming out of a sitting Democrat in 2023 uh that that's wild um yeah the bottom
line for progressives is that our reaction to the holly book can't be to think men and masculinity
is just something the right talks about there's something profound happening with American men
and the left should address it with more responsible solutions well that sounds like something
that a a spokes weasel for the patriarchy would say Chris yeah yeah fucking he is uh
we gotta get him out of there now whatever it takes get that guy out of there how crazy is it
is that that is that's going to be taken as some sort of outlandish hateful bigoted statement
it is it's cray you know we keep using the terms crazy and insane but that's the world we
fucking live in now it is absolutely i do it all the time like this is crazy like it's like
no it's fucking it's yeah it's fucking we are beyond fucking crazy now we're uh
yeah i don't know man uh oh and Benjamin did a good rant about uh you know the gender thing and
the trans shit and the uh you know this shoving it down our throats and
really how uh it's pushing sodomy on people you know because uh like he says what the
what's the difference between like uh you know i love my male friends you know and stuff we have
bonds and shit like that what makes the difference between us being buddies and gay is we don't
put it in each other's butts yeah yeah the lack of dick sucking yeah is uh what what really yeah
drives that home and and you know oh and point i mean looking at the stuff and it's now you've
seen that video come out where they're chanting we're here we're queer we're here for your
children now there's some of them chanting that here's another gas lighting thing because
you go back you look at the video because nbc or msnbc released an article saying
right wingers you know nazis or whatever saying that this video proves this or that you know
and it says that they were actually saying we're here we're queer and we're going shopping
now you can read the
Some of these people and that's what they are saying now in the article though
They're right about that part, but then the guy who organized the fucking parade says we're here. We're queer
We're here or we're gonna we're coming for your children. That's been chanted for years
It's like wait what?
As like a satire thing he says that's been chanted for years like wait, okay
So there is some people saying the shopping the people there is a crowd saying children and
The MSNBC is debunking it by saying that the obvious
There's people saying shopping and there's someone too loud saying children
But then the guy who organizes it says yeah, we're here. We're query. We're here for your children
That's said every year. That's the thing we do. It's you know, it's just part of the tradition. It's like
What the fuck it's never it's not and that's very no shit falls to like that's something they just started a couple of years ago
dude, dude and and they put this shit out and I
Mean don't read the news and shit, you know, you shouldn't read the news
It's just the fact that they gaslight the people who don't like get it
You know, they don't
Let's let's keep it in the realm of Mark Twain for a minute because he said
If you don't read the news or if you do read the news you're
If you don't read the news, you're you're uninformed if you read the news, you're missing for
Yeah, I do I did a fucking there's like a not necessarily Mark Twain forest
But where Mark Twain lived and and hung out and wrote about and all that kind of stuff in northern, California
where my kids live and there's
There's like a they preserve one of his everywhere they preserved one of his houses
Well, this is Calaveras County next to where the county next to where they live is Calaveras County
Which is that Mark Twain's, you know, the the great jumping frog and all of those stories out of there
and
Then there's a whole bunch of like Mark Twain connected spots all in in
Sonora County
Where in a lot of gold rush stuff and all kinds of shit, dude, there's some crazy ass stories that come out of there
this this whole
Area northern, California during the gold rush was just fucking out of pocket
And it's insane. What's up way that was the the Wild West
right, I
Mean you hear that the Wild West wasn't as wild as you know
They betray in movies and had to hear that from Shane Gillis. I was like, what? Let me check this out, man
It wasn't as wild as they made it out
Well, the the real wild where a lot of most of the like cowboy stories and all the Wild West stuff
That all comes from like the Dakota territories. None of that has is even very like technically West
You know these stories a lot of these towns are like gun-free towns and shit people weren't just walking around with six shooters on their fucking hips
The that's like a big point in contention in the movie Tim Stoke
Where they disarmed? Yeah, because he wanted it. Yeah
But like in Johnny Cash, man, don't take your guns guns of town
Mm-hmm, you're fucking. Yeah, you're not supposed to do that
This is a gun-free zone
Yeah, there wasn't all these fucking showdowns
You know, no that is sensationalized and some of the
Like there were a couple of you know a couple of gunslingers the same way that there are a handful of
world champion boxers
You know what I mean, and it's a much much much smaller scale in terms of that
But there and there were a lot of people who made a living
doing trick shooting
stuff like that
like
What who were some of those that chick I?
Can't remember any Oakley any Oakley and then was a wild buffalo bill. Yep. Yeah, he was a circus performer
You know, but I'd be a lot. Yeah, a lot of you people were active. There was a Hollywood actor from the I think the silent picture era
And they used to film a lot of westerns in the San Lorenzo Valley
Santa Cruz County
before before talkies
but his name was Tom mix and
He was one of those like trick shooter guys
But and he had this like jewel encrusted saddle
That he took with them everywhere and
Somebody in Felton stole it either like three or four days later. It just mysteriously returned in the middle of town
But but yeah, the the the far more far more trick shooters and whatnot
And then just also like, you know, a handful of douchebags that went around killing people because it could
Yeah
not
that
Studied up on the the Wild West as seen
Wasn't as wild as you see in the fucking, you know, like I grew up on
Young guns remember that movie. Oh, yeah
Yeah, I was more tombstone than young guns, but I remember I remember tombstone, you know, I'll be your fucking
Your whatever whatever he says your huckleberry a huckleberry buddy. I'll be your huckleberry. I
Remember the tombstone. Yeah, those west removed. I went to the theater for young guns
One and two I think
That was a little get that Lou Diamond Phillips in you
No, I
Were you there respond to that were you there for Baldy were there for Baldwin weren't you? Yeah?
Yeah
Yeah, I remember that those are the days. I mean, I think it's in Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles in the
Doing the soundtrack. Oh, yeah fucking Bon Jovi
You wanted, you know
Everybody knows the fucking one better
These streets
Wow, man, I haven't watched those movies forever
I can wild out on some westerns. I could they're they're they're fun
It's seen that you ever seen that show righteous gemstones. Yes
It's pretty good. My girl got me into that
Beginning of the year. That's just hysterical. I love me some John Goodman
There was a reference of the young guns at the end of season two
That was pretty funny. Well, it was named Danny O'Brien or with yeah. Yeah, that guy's hysterical
And I'm sure he's you know boy. They're using a lot of the
In this season a lot of the filter to make
What's his face real young?
Shit you just said his name now. I can't even John Goodman
Fucking Dan. Oh, yeah
John Goodman to make him look young make everybody look young
They're using that filter because they're doing flashbacks
And but it's like it's pretty fucking flawless
Like it's you know
Like they tried to use something like that in Star Wars and one of the last Star Wars for that dead dude
And you could totally tell like I was in the theater and it's like what the fuck there's something going on
What the hell is going on?
The tech's not there yet. It's like when when they were trying to figure out CGI fire
Hmm. Well, I mean, I think they got it in the righteous gemstones. I mean it is it's very
They used it in season two two at one point. I didn't even notice it
Like I mean, couldn't you just take you couldn't you take pre-existing?
Digital film from Roseanne and like overlay it or something like that, too
They're doing something like that like it's it's pretty flawless
I mean, it's it's and it looks like the new episode this week the whole thing is gonna be
That well, it is where are we still on the writer strike? Oh
Shit for the writers still striking because flashback episodes are a pretty good indication
That you you're not you don't have your a team writing the scripts because you can't think of anything new you've all you've got a you know
Well, I mean that the gemstones is it's really like how the fuck did they get to where they're at, you know?
Yeah, that's because it starts off with they're already where they're at
Yeah, so they're in the which the writer strike I keep forgetting about it because I don't really watch TV like
You know, so I'm saying I'm asking cuz I don't have an answer for that. I don't know
I don't know either. So I I didn't even know the gemstones are on until like last week
I already missed like a couple episodes because
Someone posted on Twitter about the gemstones like oh shit. That's back on sweet, you know, cuz it's just with Outlander
Outlander, I don't even know what that is. It takes place in like
Salem witch trial times and there's some time traveling dr
lady. Yeah. It's like Doctor Who for
chicks. It's all it's all tragedy porn. It
is. Come on. Walk into a room and she's
all misty. Like what the fuck? Just stop
watching that shit. It's bad for you.
It's like the romantic movies, you know,
create this fucking false reality of
relationships and shit. They got this
bitch traveling back to the future to
go grab some other bitch to go back into
the past to go perform some complicated
medical surgery that you know is gonna
get you burned at the stake. You know
it is. Outlander. I mean, is that like a
spinoff of Highlander? No. Oddly, it's
not. Weird. And that's kind of what I
thought, too. We're gonna see, you
know, couple of sword wielding long
hair, freaking stretched out Ronnie
James Dio's or something like that.
Yeah. No, I've never heard of it. No,
my girl probably watches it. She
watches weird shit. Dude, I noticed
that everything she watches every time
I walk in, it's a gay scene. And I
just fucking shake my head. She's
like, what? And I'm like, every
fucking time every, they have to
put it in there. It's like, do they
though? Do they really do? They have
to put two dudes fucking making out
and like, because last time I checked,
it's ridiculous. That's still not even
representative of 10% of the
population, let alone 10% every fucking
time on the screen, man. When I
because she watches, I bet she
watches this outlander. I'll have
to ask her. I bet she's already
watched our fucking many episodes
right. Right. Dude. I don't know, man.
I'm like, what's up? I said, I'm
going the other direction. And
tomorrow we've got slotted into after
we're done with work for the day.
Building shit. We're going to geek
out on some attack on Titan. That's
that's where the direction we're
going. All right. Like in anime.
It's a very, it's actually from a
sociological perspective. It's a
really interesting show. It is.
And it's done really well. There's
only a handful, really, that I've
ever gone for. And I'd be like
cowboy bebop from back in the day.
I enjoyed quite a bit. The eon
flux shit that you could see on what
was the adult flux that was like
fucking brutally violent, right?
Yeah, dude. Yeah. And it was, you
know, almost 30 years ago or
something like that. When they
dropped out on adult swim, there
was some, you know, a handful of
those. The original like Princess
Mononoke was freaking crazy. But
then, you know, I got I stopped
giving a shit about it because I
was a fucking adult and do it now
that my kids are what there's some
good anime and most of it shit, but
like the Demon Slayer series is
pretty cool for, you know, younger
kids and then attack on Titan is
wild. It is fun spot to check
that out. Glory Jones, my
maybe now that I'm older, I'll
be like, this is pretty sweet.
You know, yeah, dude. Yeah,
there's I mean, and what you can
do with animation and what you
can say in animation is always
so much more wild than what you
can do with with even with
fucking, you know, yeah, I can't
remember which one I was watching.
Because I think they have like
that's this new one on Netflix
and I flipped it on. And it
was violent as fuck. Like
immediately someone's just
chopping people into fucking
people a whole. It was almost
like a kill bill scene, but
in color and in detail.
I guess the put off on with me
and animates how it's like
those, you know, and like, they're
flying through the air and just
the the background's kind of the
motion and only the eyes and the
mouth move. It's like a simple
animation, but still very
extremely detailed and very, you
know. Yeah, I'll have to
check that out. It's pretty cool.
It is. It is. And I don't have to
check it out. I don't typically
talk up much of much of
anything that's available like
that. But no, it's been fun as
for sure. I have some time on
my hands. Did you see this
thing where? Yeah, that's
true. That's true.
Did you see this thing where
they're talking about
or there's this like random
billionaire that is talking
about all save you CNN.
Save you CNN. Yeah. Yeah.
He wants to buy CNN because
they're they're failing so bad.
John Katz, a meddys the OK.
So is he a new billion?
He must be a new billionaire.
No, he's a hundred and some
billionaires made the last two
years. He's he's a grocery
store magnate.
I guess I've never heard of
Dagestino. So he probably did
get into the billionaire club
just in the last two, three
years. If he runs a supermarket
chain with the inflation, with
maybe the run up in covid
and shit. I don't know, man.
He's like he's he looks like
he's comfortable for a while.
Yeah. Well, yeah, comfortable.
I mean, you don't have to be
a billionaire and you'd be
comfortable.
Were you saying about RFK?
He definitely did those kids
probably, you know.
Anyways, RFK, you know,
RFK, he'll rattle out these
fucking, you know, stats
and these fucking facts.
And then you check them out.
I mean, when he was talking
about, you know, all the money
stolen over the course of covid,
all the billionaires made the
shift thing and all that shit.
I mean, yeah, I don't know
what to make of the dude because
it's like a soft disclosure
type thing. I really like that
term, the soft disclosure.
It's better than using
revelations of the method type
shit, you know, because that's
what it is. It's like
it's this soft disclosing
here. We're we're going to tell
we're going to allow someone to
have a platform to tell you all
the facts.
We're going to demonize them at
the same time.
And then, you know,
we told you and
what are you going to do about
it? Here's your president, Joe
Biden, you know, he just got
81 million votes.
Right?
Like that's fair.
Yeah.
So.
So this dude, this
dude, he's a new he's a new
billionaire. 4.1.
Because OK, entrepreneur politician,
radio show host besides grocery
stores, his holdings include real
estate firm and aviation company
and oil refinery and the Hellenic
Times newspaper.
Yeah, he might be a new
billionaire.
Yeah, he owns the radio station
W. A. B. C. A. M.
770, his radio station.
Oh, host the the Cats Roundtable.
OK.
Yeah. And then he wants to buy
CNN and get paid.
Is CNN money wise?
I was asking if CNN is even for
sale. Like, right, it's
all for sale.
Well, yeah.
Primetime viewerships down a
quarter annual profits have
slipped by a lot
almost almost half.
Investment bankers believe the
outlet could be sold for five to
six billion if it's put on the
market.
Wow, which clearly he does not
have the.
It's going to have to get some
Saudis to invest or something.
Well, you know,
look, if if a random
Saudi prince doesn't have a stake
in your media old company,
you're just not doing it right.
You're not. You're not.
Why not get a couple of Chinese
firms? Make sure the Vanguard and
BlackRock are in there, too.
Why not? Jeff Bezos and Bill Gates
better head your bets.
Go with Warren Buffett and Richard
Branson, too.
Now we're getting somewhere.
And they're just, you know,
them throwing out
the headline like billionaire wants
to buy CNN.
He's kind of in the median
shit, you know, as far as
the industry. It's not like just
some random dude
who's not in that
area of propaganda
is just, you know, trying to
brand of buy CNN.
It's not like fucking Kevin
who is a brand new billionaire.
He might have been a billionaire,
but his billions definitely got
fucking grown to that four billion
this last year. He's probably one
billionaire or something, you know,
but the old fucking
Kevin who fucking cashed in
on crypto or something and fucking
somehow fucking got
billions of dollars.
Yeah, they fucking
I don't even know where I was going
with that. It's been a long week,
Steve. No, I get it.
I get it. Me, too.
Me, too. I had to fucking
yeah.
Sort of thinking about these
billionaires like fuck these guys.
Maybe the communists.
They're fucking real fucking
world problems.
There's no such thing as a good
one. Let's get rid of them.
Fucking robot motherfuckers.
The whole.
fucking Twitter thing it's got to be fucking crazy to have I mean if he owns
really owns Twitter you know and sit really sitting there changing the fucking
codes and shit and tweeting out you you got a limit and like my Twitter like I
said on the mobile fucking doesn't even fucking work I have to use it on the
PC I can't you have uninstalled it reinstalled it killed the cash fucking
everything you can do with it it will not let me use the motherfucker so yeah
whatever but they just launched that Facebook saying you know it are they
fucking with Twitter to push into Facebook you know is I mean they're gonna
fight each other and fuck out of here it's so so fucking cartoonish man it
really is it's like the world robot wars and I know I'm gonna get a comedy
I know I'm gonna have a bootleg link I know that I'm probably gonna watch at
least the undercard I'm gonna watch it I'm gonna watch and I'm sure that I'll
end up watching you know whatever stage show they put on for that you know
they've got like the best professional wrestling trainers with them for this
shit nobody's actually getting hurt yeah it's not gonna happen it's it's like
the 2024 elections it's not gonna happen right at least not not in the way that
it's advertised not in the way that it's marketed it's definitely not gonna go
down that way it's gonna move into the metaverse right right they're gonna
box in the metaverse take place in the metaverse and they'll both have them
hooked up to augmented reality things yeah and that's how they'll do it shit
we just put that out there well when it happens they people can say we heard
it here first on a and wake up yeah yeah yeah because that's probably where it's
going you know it's funny is I tweeted like the day before alright as I
messaged someone and I was like yo there's something going on with Twitter
maybe they're enacting these limits for non-paid and paid and then fucking
Elon tweets out there's a limit for paid non-paid and fucking new users
we've shut it down to where I just started using this new download video
downloader now I can't use it because you have to sign in to Twitter to fucking
view the videos which is stupid you know and then they come out and they say oh
it's for your good it's for the greater good it's to stop scraping they
already scraped it yeah yeah they already scraped it you know like I never
hit no fucking limits I said fuck you Elon I'm gonna read everybody's tweets now
right ones I will circumvent this by not participating in app yeah so I now I'm
gonna fucking read them all haha suck it musk I'm out here read 600 but that's
just crazy though I don't know how many it's a lot I heard people legitimately
legitimately make the argument well in order to preserve actual free speech
we've got a really clamped down because they're scraping the internet guys so
we got to clamp down on what you're fucking saying and posting so that way
we can stop the bots that have already scraped everything off the fucking
internet you know yeah like and people are you know there's some video
going around is some dude saying you know it's oh he really put a wrench and
fucking DARPA's gears yeah okay sure sure a guy who is subsidized by DARPA it
really put a wrench in DARPA's you get oh god the fuck out usually when you slam
your head that's fucking retarded yes 100% exactly what that is
it's fucking ridiculous man dude is there bots on rumble now start to take a
roll well I've never seen bots in your chat before but now there's this fucking
one that keeps pot throwing this link to which I would not don't click on that
link guys the red suns in oil no it's for some Tucker Carlson podcast with
Donald Trump interesting I'm sure it's not or the rumble chat the rumble chat
interesting oh yeah no I see it now I do I do it's the first time I've seen like a
spam bot let's get rid of it in one of the chat yeah need mods in the fucking
rumbles you user I do read the rumble I try to read the rumble there we go later
I'm glad with it yeah well let's keep the bots down on the platform for sure for
sure yeah and look I read the rumble I just don't read it off I don't read the
other chat often either I don't it's hard to keep it's hard to read the rumble
it's hard to read the chat because like when me and Shep are going on with on
YouTube in the chats going and we're trying to bring up and show that the
comments on the screen it's fucking hard to keep up I mean love you in the chat
though but it's hard it's hard to keep up yeah no it takes you entirely out
of the show if you're in the chat mmm and it says you can't unless you
specifically are stopping the flow of what you're doing to read or to address
something it's just it's not really conducive to yeah and I have today I'm
pretty off hey I'm feeling human for like mildly human for the first time in a
minute man and I just yeah I'm still like half out of it source fucking have to
immediately go to work as soon as we're done here which we're basically done
here so yeah I have that get ready to travel fill in gravity yeah yeah that's
literally just what plays in my head when I think about it it's really nothing else
like in the play well sad trombone aside where where can people keep up with you
and I assume you're putting out content every day right now not yet I mean I'm
good I'll be doing my show this weekend I skipped on my show last weekend I'll be
out this weekend Sunday 7 p.m. Ron rumble rain out rancas.com go to my
rumble.com slash C slash rain out rancas follow me there that's the only
place I stream the live videos that and yeah I mean depending on how long I'm
gonna be you know where I'm at right if I'm gonna I was thinking about starting
a live show eight o'clock every night seven or eight o'clock every night just
so I can rant about you know the day's bullshit because nobody in my house
wants to hear it so right yeah no I get that I get that I do well cool man well
guys make sure you're doing that there was a rumble rant from Vicki Lynn thank you
very much great quote from me in the show
hell yeah history begins whenever it's politically convenient always good stuff
on a wake-up thank you very much there was a last-minute or a late Super Ray 2 I
think let me go up to that and check that Greg Steve that code could be a bomb and
it could blow it's true Mariah Myers I am wake-up rocks much love thank you
Mariah appreciate you and then Robert on the Venmo thank you very much
appreciate that you guys that's gonna do it for the week no Friday shows while my
kids are here because they've been here for like a month now and I've barely hung
out with them it seems like it seems like it like even though we're in the
same space we're all doing shit and it's not yet it's family Friday's yeah
gonna give that a family Friday's gonna give that a shot will probably be on
the critical hour panel though that's a half an hour of radio out of the day that's
you know that's forgivable well oh I have a thing tonight I think I'm gonna be on
reality's ours tonight I haven't done that show before and looking forward to
that and then what we got a hold of their slim got a hold of me and he's
now able to like catch up and look at his schedule and we're gonna get the
the weekly segment thing going and coordinated over the weekend so that
will most likely start next week and we'll be doing weekly beef intelligence
and food intelligence in general segments with good old Texas Slim what
else I think that's about it I think so I don't know if I can think of
anything else I'll say it later but you guys are freaking awesome thank Chris
thanks to
me on John Kiri Aku for joining us this morning. Um, and yeah,
stick around, lots of good stuff coming up newsletter will come
out tomorrow. And I will have location details for the July
meetup for snow mechanic. And if you guys, you are totally
encouraged to start your own meetups, whether it's for
this show or for any other fucking read, connect with
people in in 3D, it's very important. Mm hmm. Yeah, but
um that'll do it for me and uh and we'll see you next week,
you guys. Good luck to us all.